<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<tv generator-info-name="EPG dostarcza http://kodiwpigulce.pl" generator-info-url="http://epg.ovh @sky02, @azman, @Max1000"><channel id="Stingray Classica">
    <display-name lang="pl">Stingray Classica</display-name>
    <display-name lang="pl">Stingray Classica PL</display-name>
    <display-name lang="pl">Stingray Classica HD</display-name>
    <icon src="http://epg.ovh/logo/Stingray+Classica.png" />
    <url>http://www.epg.ovh</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="MEZZO">
    <display-name lang="pl">MEZZO</display-name>
    <display-name lang="pl">MEZZO HD</display-name>
    <display-name lang="pl">MEZZO FHD</display-name>
    <display-name lang="pl">MEZZO PL</display-name>
    <display-name lang="pl">MEZZO FHD PL</display-name>
    <display-name lang="pl">MEZZO HD PL</display-name>
    <icon src="http://epg.ovh/logo/MEZZO.png" />
    <url>http://www.epg.ovh</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Sport 1">
    <display-name lang="cs">Sport 1</display-name>
    <icon src="http://epg.ovh/logo/Sport+1.png" />
    <url>http://www.epg.ovh</url>
  </channel>
  <channel id="Sport 2">
    <display-name lang="cs">Sport 2</display-name>
    <icon src="http://epg.ovh/logo/Sport+2.png" />
    <url>http://www.epg.ovh</url>
  </channel>
  <programme start="20260305000000 +0100" stop="20260305020100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Dvorák - Rusalka</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Opéra de Limoges, France. Bulgarian conductor Pavel Baleff conducts the Orchestra and Choir of the Opéra de Limoges in a performance of Antonín Dvorák's lyric fairytale opera Rusalka (1900). The work's libretto is written by Czech poet Jaroslav Kvapil. Rusalka, an elusive water nymph, falls in love with the Prince, who happens to swim in her lake. Rusalka longs to become human herself so that she can be together with the Prince. The witch Jezibaba is willing to help Rusalka, but warns her that the transition to a mortal human being comes at a high price: the nymph will lose the power of speech. What is more, if mute Rusalka cannot keep the love of a human, she will be damned for eternity. Stage director Nicola Raab and TV director Arnaud Lalanne created a truly filmic production of Dvorák's masterpiece. Among the soloists are Ruzan Mantashyan, Adam Smith, Rafal Pawnuk, Marie-Adeline Henry, Marion Lebegue, and Alexandra Marcellier. This performance was recorded at the Opéra de Limoges, France, in February 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>16</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305020100 +0100" stop="20260305031500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">A Mozart Concert from Berlin</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Konzerthaus Berlin, Germany. The Carl Philipp Emanuel Bach Chamber Orchestra delivers a program entirely devoted to Mozart at the Konzerthaus in Berlin under the direction of Hartmut Haenchen. In reduced form, the ensemble manages to bring to life the many characteristics of the music and the unique spirit of the famous composer, be it his gaiety of heart, his lyricism, his dramatic side or his polyphonic writing inspired. Criticism has always praised Carl Philipp Emanuel Bach's stylistic assurance, transparency of textures and technical precision. The extraordinary sensitivity and ease of Stefan Vladar make him an ideal partner for Haenchen and his orchestra. The evening's program includes Divertimento, K. 113; the Concerto for Piano and Orchestra No. 20, K. 466, and Symphony No. 41, K. 551.</desc>
    <date>2005</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305031500 +0100" stop="20260305041000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">In Rehearsal: Zubin Mehta</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Tel Aviv, Israel. Indian conductor Zubin Mehta (1936) became Music Director of the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra (IPO) in 1977 and was appointed Music Director for Life in 1981. On July 18, 1996, Mehta led the IPO in its first-ever performance of Richard Strauss's tone poem Till Eulenspiegels lustige Streiche, Op. 28. Renowned as one of the world's foremost interpreters of the great symphonic repertoire-especially the Romantic works of Anton Bruckner, Gustav Mahler, and Richard Strauss-Mehta had conducted this popular masterpiece many times before. However, this was the first occasion he rehearsed it from the very beginning with the orchestra. This episode of 'In Rehearsal' offers an intimate look at the dialogue between Mehta and the musicians as they explore Strauss's tone poem together.</desc>
    <date>1996</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305041000 +0100" stop="20260305050600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 3 in E-flat major, Op. 55</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305050600 +0100" stop="20260305053200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2021 - Semi-finals: Fauré, Wolf a. o</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Het Noordbrabants Museum, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Soprano Alisa Fedorenko (Russia, 1999) and pianist Evgenii Sergeev (Russia, 1986) perform 'Mandoline' and 'A Clymene' from Gabriel Fauré's Cinq melodies "de Venise", Op. 58; 'Lied der Delphine' from Franz Schubert's Zwei Szenen aus dem Schauspiel 'Lacrimas', D. 857; 'Son' (A dream) from Sergei Rachmaninoff's Six Romances, Op. 38; 'Elfenlied' from Hugo Wolf's Mörike-Lieder; 'Staccato' from Rodion Shchedrin's Three solfege exercises; and Bart Visman's Vermeer's Gold, during the semi-finals of the International Vocal Competition 2021 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Het Noordbrabants Museum in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305053200 +0100" stop="20260305060000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305060000 +0100" stop="20260305063600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 27, KV 595</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Schönbrunn Palace, Vienna. Soloist Aleksander Madzar and the Royal Philharmonic Orchestra directed by Andre Previn join forces in a performance of Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 27, KV 595, recorded at Vienna's Schönbrunn palace. In 1791, with his life cruelly and rapidly ending, Mozart once again turned to the compositional style which reflected his personality: the concerto for piano and orchestra. His last piano concerto, which turned out to be an uplifting composition, regales its audience with a lyrical children's song, invoking the joys of youth and springtime.</desc>
    <date>1990</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305063600 +0100" stop="20260305070300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bruch - Violin Concerto No. 1, Op. 26</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Tchaikovsky Conservatory, Moscow. Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berliner Philharmonic during the 2008 edition of the Europakonzert, held in the renowned hall of the Tchaikovsky Conservatory in Moscow. The first edition of the Europakonzert was in 1991, and since then, the founding of the Berlin Philharmonic on May 1st in 1882 is annually celebrated with a concert in a European city of cultural significance. The orchestra opens with an outstanding performance of Stravinsky's Symphony in Three Movements. Furthermore, Vadim Repin, one of today's most fascinating artists, features as soloist in Bruch's Concerto for Violin No. 1, Op, 26. The orchestra concludes with a performance of Beethoven's Symphony No. 7, of which the second movement, Allegretto, gained instant popularity after its premiere in 1813 and remains a crowd favorite.</desc>
    <date>2008</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305070300 +0100" stop="20260305075500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Shusha Renaissance (2023)</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Azerbaijan. "Shusha, the Renaissance" is a musical journey featuring pianist Murad Huseynov. The city of Shusha is often considered the cradle of Azerbaijan's music and poetry and one of the leading centres of the Azerbaijani culture, having been declared the cultural capital of Azerbaijan in January 2021. On the program are the following works: Fikret Amirov's (1922-1984) Twelve Miniatures for Piano Solo: I. Ballade - II. Ashigsayagi - III. Nocturne - IV. Humoresque - V. Lyrical Dance - VI. Hunting - VII. Lullaby - VIII. Waltz - IX. Barcarolle - X. Toccata - XI. Elegy - XII. March; Adil Babirov's (1934-2021) 's Prelude &amp; Scherzo; Gara Garayev's (1918-1982) Sonatine: I. Allegro - II. Moderato assai - III. Vivo ; Tofik Kouliyev's (1917-2000) 'Gaytagi' and F. Amirov's Romantic Sonata: I. Allegro energico - II. Andante espressivo - III. Allegro non troppo). This performance is filmed in Shusha in October 2023 and in the Heydar Aliyev Center, Baku, in December 2023. Written and directed by Michel Swierczewski.</desc>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305075500 +0100" stop="20260305081900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2021 - Semi-finals: Brahms, Britten a. o</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Het Noordbrabants Museum, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Soprano Vassia Alati (the Netherlands/Greece, 1992) and pianist Yuto Kiguchi (Japan, 1989) perform 'C'est l'extase langoureuse' from Claude Debussy's Arriettes oubliées, L. 63, and 'Fantoches' from Debussy's Fetes galantes, L. 86; Bart Visman's Het goud van Vermeer; 'Lerchengesang' from Johannes Brahms's Vier Gesänge, Op. 70; Franz Schubert's Gruppe aus dem Tartarus, Op. 24, No. 1, D. 583; 'Now the leaves are falling fast' from Benjamin Britten's On this island, Op. 11; and 'I gria zoi' (Old mother life) from Manolis Kalomiris's Mayovotana (Magic herbs), during the semi-finals of the International Vocal Competition 2021 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Het Noordbrabants Museum in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305081900 +0100" stop="20260305091700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Pierre Boulez - A life for music</title>
    <desc lang="pl">France. The French musician and composer Pierre Boulez (1925-2016) is considered one of the most influential figures in twentieth-century music. In the documentary 'Pierre Boulez - A life of music' (2017), Reiner E. Moritz creates a personal portrait of the young and impatient artist who once impetuously suggested to blow up the opera houses in order to do away with stuffy traditions, yet later moved on to conduct the "Ring of the Century" in the very heart of traditional opera, Bayreuth, and became a prized guest conductor with the world´s greatest orchestras. The documentary includes fragments from the composer's rich oeuvre, and features rare photographs from the Boulez-Chevalier archive. The documentary is at its most personal when the maestro's family and friends reflect on his life. Boulez's younger brother Roger shares invaluable information about Pierre's early years, and the renowned pianist Daniel Barenboim opens up about his friend's music and compositions.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305091700 +0100" stop="20260305093800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">PIAM - Semi-final: Mendelssohn and Chopin</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Nuovo Teatro Ariberto, Milan, Italy. Acclaimed classical music talent scout Antonio Mormone (1930-2017) lives on as the name-giver of the Premio Internazionale Antonio Mormone (PIAM), awarded to the winner of the Italian music competition of the same name. The first edition of this competition, which was held in various venues in Milan from 2019 to 2021, was dedicated to the piano. As part of this competition, Leonardo Colafelice (Italy, 1995) performs Felix Mendelssohn's Variations sérieuses, Op. 54, and Frédéric Chopin's "Heroic" Polonaise in A-flat major, Op. 53. This performance was recorded at Nuovo Teatro Ariberto in Milan, in May, 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305093800 +0100" stop="20260305100000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305100000 +0100" stop="20260305105700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">How to get out of the Cage - A year with John Cage</title>
    <desc lang="pl">United States. The compelling documentary How to Get Out of the Cage (2012) by award-winning filmmaker Frank Scheffer presents an intimate portrait of John Cage (1912-1992), one of 20th century's most important composers. From 1982 to 1992, Scheffer worked with Cage on numerous occasions, which resulted in unique archives of historical audio-visual material, including interviews, musical performances, and images of locations related to the composer's life and work. In all Scheffer's works related to Cage, he used the old Chinese method of chance operations based on the Yi Jing - as often used by Cage himself in his compositions. Instead of using chance operations, Scheffer edited the film in the usual way that is based on choice.</desc>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305105700 +0100" stop="20260305112600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Divertimento No. 11, K. 251</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Lucerne Culture and Congress Center (KKL), Switzerland. The soloists from the Lucerne Festival Orchestra present Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's Divertimento No. 11 in D major, K. 251, known as the 'Nannerl-Septet'. Mozart composed it in 1776, probably on the occasion of his sister Maria Anna's name day, whose nickname was 'Nannerl'. The septet is scored for oboe, two horns, two violins, viola and double bass. This performance was recorded at Lucerne Culture and Congress Center (KKL), Switzerland, in 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305112600 +0100" stop="20260305121900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Requiem in D minor, K. 626</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino, Florence, Italy. Daniel Harding leads the Orchestra and Choir of the Maggio Musicale Fiorentino and four vocal soloists in a magnificent performance of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's Requiem in D minor, K. 626. The soloists are soprano Christiane Karg, mezzosoprano Sara Mingardo, tenor Matthew Swensen, and bass Gianluca Buratto. The Austrian Count Walsegg commissioned Mozart to compose a Requiem in July 1791 to commemorate his late wife, Anna. At the time, Mozart was busy working on his operas La clemenza di Tito and The Magic Flute. By the time he started on the Requiem, in the fall of that same year, his health was seriously declining. Mozart passed away in December 1791, leaving the Requiem uncompleted. His pupil Franz Xaver Süssmayr completed Mozart's swan song in the form known today, based on Mozart's sketches and possibly verbal instructions. This performance was recorded at Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in Florence, Italy, in 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305121900 +0100" stop="20260305132000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Works by Gluck, Bach and Mozart</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Auditorio Sony, Reina Sofía School of Music, Madrid, Spain. Venezuelan-born conductor Giovanni Guzzo leads the Camerata Fundación EDP of the Reina Sofía School of Music in a spirited concert. The program opens with the ethereal 'Danza degli spiriti beati' (Dance of the Blessed Spirits) from Christoph Willibald Gluck's opera Orfeo ed Euridice, featuring flutist Matthew Raymond Origel. The concert continues with vocal masterworks, including J.S. Bach's brilliant cantata aria 'Jauchzet Gott in allen Landen!', BWV 51, featuring soprano Marlin González Zúniga and trumpeter Marc Ferrando Pelegrí, and W.A. Mozart's joyous motet Exsultate, jubilate, K. 165, sung by soprano Carla Isabel Gómez del Pulgar. The concert concludes with one of the great classical works: Mozart's dramatic Symphony No. 40 in G minor. This performance was recorded at Auditorio Sony of the Reina Sofía School of Music in Madrid, Spain, on December 18, 2024.</desc>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305132000 +0100" stop="20260305140000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">PIAM - Semi-final: Rameau, Liszt and Chopin</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Auditorium Giorgio Gaber, Milan, Italy. Acclaimed classical music talent scout Antonio Mormone (1930-2017) lives on as the name-giver of the Premio Internazionale Antonio Mormone (PIAM), awarded to the winner of the Italian music competition of the same name. The first edition of this competition, which was held in various venues in Milan from 2019 to 2021, was dedicated to the piano. As part of this competition, Leonardo Pierdomenico (Italy, 1994) performs Gavotte et six doubles from Jean-Philippe Rameau's Suite in A minor, RCT 5, and Franz Liszt's Sonata in B minor. As an encore, Pierdomenico plays Frédéric Chopin's Etude Op. 10 No. 1. This performance was recorded at Auditorium Giorgio Gaber in Milan, in December 2019.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305140000 +0100" stop="20260305145200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Porpora - Neapolitan &amp; Cosmopolitan</title>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305145200 +0100" stop="20260305155400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Pletnev conducts Bizet &amp; Ravel's Concerto No. 1</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Tchaikovsky Concert Hall, Moscow, Russia. Mikhail Pletnev leads the Russian National Orchestra (RNO) in a performance of Maurice Ravel's Piano Concerto No. 1 with Lucas Debargue as the soloist. The concert opens with a selection of music by Georges Bizet based on Alphonse Daudet's play 'L'Arlésienne'. The music is compiled by Mikhail Pletnev. The first movement of Ravel's Piano Concerto No. 1 contains five distinctive themes, of which three are reminiscent of jazz. Debargue's performance of Ravel's concerto is followed by Gabriel Fauré's Barcarolle No. 4. The performance was recorded at Tchaikovsky Concert Hall in Moscow as part of the Ninth RNO Grand Festival.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305155400 +0100" stop="20260305170900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bruckner - Symphony No. 4</title>
    <desc lang="pl">St. Florian's Monastery, Austria. When it comes to shaping a musical event for the ears and the eyes, the monumental majesty of Anton Bruckner's (1824-1896) symphonies and the exhilarating vibrancy of St. Florian's monastery are a perfect match - especially when they are captured on film so thrillingly by such an eminent director as Brian Large in 2012. Bruckner became acquainted with the monastery's organ in his childhood and served as the organist there from 1845 to 1855. Welser-Möst, the principal conductor of the Cleveland Orchestra and General Music Director of the Vienna State Opera, is an acknowledged Bruckner specialist who has developed a passion for the composer's Fourth Symphony - called the "Romantic" by its creator - in its infrequently played first edition (1888/89). More slender, dynamic and finely shaded than the more commonly performed version, this score is also more daring, with its sharper contrasts and boldly exposed dissonances. Recorded at the St. Florian Monastery in Austria, in 2012.</desc>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305170900 +0100" stop="20260305184700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Waldbühne 2004 - Tchaikovsky night</title>
    <date>2004</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305184700 +0100" stop="20260305185900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Liszt - Elegies No. 1 and 2 (S. 130 &amp; 131)</title>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305185900 +0100" stop="20260305195500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">In Rehearsal: Esa-Pekka Salonen</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Dorothy Chandler Pavilion, Music Center of Los Angeles County, USA. The Finnish composer and conductor Esa-Pekka Salonen (1958) was Music Director of the Los Angeles Philharmonic from 1992 until 2009. Under his dynamic leadership, it was recognized as one of the world's most outstanding orchestras. The exciting musical partnership Salonen established with his musicians was widely acclaimed in the international press. The conductor's lucidity, efficiency, and lack of pretension, promoted a relaxed collaboration between himself and the orchestra, which is particularly evident in the rehearsal process. This 'In Rehearsal' episode features Salonen rehearsing Claude Debussy's Impressionistic orchestral piece La Mer with the Los Angeles Philharmonic at the Dorothy Chandler Pavilion of the Music Center of Los Angeles County. It gives a fascinating insight into Salonen's rapport with his musicians and also into Debussy's masterpiece.</desc>
    <date>1997</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305195500 +0100" stop="20260305205000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Brahms - Violin Concerto &amp; Academic Ouverture</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Severance Hall, Cleveland, USA. One of today's most distinguished conductors, Franz Welser-Möst conducts The Cleveland Orchestra in a performance featuring works from the oeuvre of Johannes Brahms. The concert begins with the Academic Festival Overture, written in honor of the University of Breslau, which awarded the composer an honorary doctorate in philosophy. This is followed by Brahms only Violin Concerto (in D major), described by violinist Joseph Joachim, whom it was originally written for, as one of the four great German violin concerti. This performance features violin soloist Julia Fischer. It was recorded at Severance Hall in Cleveland, USA, in 2014.</desc>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305205000 +0100" stop="20260305210100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305210100 +0100" stop="20260305223600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Delibes - Coppélia</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro La Fenice, Venice. A classic French ballet, Coppélia was choreographed in 1870 at the Opera de Paris, drawing inspiration from the evolution of society and the choreographer's imagination. Featuring 40 dancers, the action takes place in the America of Fred Astaire, Gene Kelly, and Jérôme Robbins and echoes the style and spirit of Broadway musicals and Hollywood fantasies. This modern and fast-paced version was performed by Ballet de l'Opéra national de Bordeaux at the Teatro La Fenice in Venice in 2010.</desc>
    <date>2010</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>12</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305223600 +0100" stop="20260305231700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Piano Concerto No. 5, 'Emperor</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Barbican Hall, London, UK. Italian conductor Gianandrea Noseda leads the London Symphony Orchestra (LSO) in a performance of Ludwig van Beethoven's Piano Concerto No. 5 in E-flat major, Op. 73, famously known as the 'Emperor' Concerto. Italian pianist Beatrice Rana features as the soloist here. The New York Times describes her as 'one of the most insightful and prodigiously gifted artists of the new generation'. Beethoven's Fifth Piano Concerto opens with a grand, majestic chord followed by a brilliant flourish from the piano, setting the tone for one of the most celebrated works in the piano repertoire. Composed between 1809 and 1811, it reflects Beethoven's heroic spirit during a turbulent period in European history and is admired for its boldness, lyricism, and virtuosic demands. This concert was recorded at London's Barbican Hall, UK, on February 2, 2022.</desc>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305231700 +0100" stop="20260305234000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Sinding - Serenade in A major, Op. 92</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro Comunale Citta di Vicenza, Italy. Violinists Francesca Dego and Domenico Nordio and pianist Andrea Bacchetti perform Serenade in A major, Op. 92 by Norwegian composer Christian Sinding (1856-1941). Together with Edvard Grieg, Sinding was Norway's best-known composer at the turn of the century. Composing in the late Romantic style, Sinding's oeuvre includes a large number of piano pieces, chamber music, and songs. The composer wrote two serenades for two violins and piano: Op. 56 and Op. 92. His Serenade Op. 92 dates from 1909 and consists, like his other Serenade, of five movements. This performance was recorded at Teatro Comunale Citta di Vicenza, Italy, on December 2, 2013.</desc>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305234000 +0100" stop="20260306000000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2010</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306000000 +0100" stop="20260306022400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Donizetti - L'elisir d'amore</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro Donizetti, Bergamo, Italy. Riccardo Frizza conducts the Orchestra Gli Originali and the Coro Donizetti Opera in a performance of Geatano Donizetti's comic opera L'elisir d'amore ('The Elixer of Love', 1832). L'elisir d'amore is perhaps the most famous work in Donizetti's extensive repertoire. It tells the story of the poor peasant Nemorino who is in love with the beautiful landowner Adina. After hearing about the legend of Tristan and Isolde, the desperate Nemorino wonders if a love potion would help him to gain Adina's love. He seeks help of the travelling quack Dr. Dulcamara, from whom he purchases a bottle of magic elixir. Directed by Frederic Wake-Walker, this 2021 production is unique as it features the complete, original score as reconstructed by Alberto Zedda based on Donizetti's autographs. In addition, the orchestra plays on historical instruments to recreate the sound of Donizetti's orchestra. Among the soloists are Caterina Sala (Adina), Javier Camarena (Nemorino), Florian Sempey (Belcore), Roberto Frontali (Dulcamara), Anais Mejías (Giannetta), and Manuel Ferreira (Master of ceremonies). This performance was part of the Donizetti Opera Festival, recorded at Teatro Donizetti in Bergamo, Italy, in 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>12</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306022400 +0100" stop="20260306040800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Abbado conducts Mahler and Schönberg</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Musikverein Vienna, Austria. The program is introduced with a short documentation about Schönberg's Pelleas et Melisande, based on a text by Claudio Abbado. Every musical theme relates to a special colour appearing on screen. What has been so remarkable about Abbado's Mahler performances is that their impact has never been achieved at the expense of the multiple sensitivities, subtleties and extreme sophistication. Together with the world's leading youth orchestra - the Gustav Mahler Jugendorchester (GMJO) - Abbado performs Mahler's Symphony No. 4 and Schönberg's Pelleas und Melisande, Op. 5. The Gustav Mahler Jugendorchester was founded in Vienna in 1986, by Abbado's initiative. The orchestra's high level of artistic quality and its international success have moved important conductors and soloists to work with the ensemble.</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306040800 +0100" stop="20260306050300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">In Rehearsal: Mariss Jansons</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Oslo Concert Hall, Norway. Latvian maestro Mariss Jansons (1943-2019) was one of the world's leading conductors. He served as Music Director of the Oslo Philharmonic from 1979 to 2000, during which time he transformed the orchestra into a front-rank ensemble. Under his leadership, the orchestra toured extensively and became a favorite at major festivals worldwide. The Oslo Philharmonic was celebrated for its fresh, open sound and for Jansons's passionate interpretations of works by Dmitri Shostakovich, Richard Strauss, Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky, and Béla Bartók. In this episode of 'In Rehearsal,' Jansons guides the orchestra through the powerful Suite from Bartók's pantomime ballet The Miraculous Mandarin, culminating in a performance at the Oslo Concert Hall.</desc>
    <date>1997</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306050300 +0100" stop="20260306053400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Lang Lang - The Third Dimension</title>
    <date>2010</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306053400 +0100" stop="20260306054900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Telemann - Jesus liegt in letzten Zügen, TWV 1:983</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Alte Oper Frankfurt, Germany. The film Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann is a portrait of a very special vocalist, and of two exceptional composers. When Philippe Jaroussky - whose angelic voice seems almost timeless, not belonging to any one epoque or decade - sings works by Telemann and Bach, it becomes abundantly clear that the sheer emotional force and the purifying power of their music have not diminished over the centuries. The works performed in this film are Telemann's Jesus liegt in letzten Zügen and Sinfonia from Brockes-Passion; Der am Ölberg zagende Jesus, and Bach's Sinfonia from Ich hatte viel Bekümmernis and Ich habe genug.</desc>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306054900 +0100" stop="20260306060000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306060000 +0100" stop="20260306063300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Symphony No. 36, K. 425</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Schloss Schönbrunn, Vienna. Jeffrey Tate conducts the English Chamber Orchestra in a performance of W. A. Mozart's "Linzer" Symphony No. 36 (K. 425). The broadcast is directed by János Darvas. Mozart composed the work in 1783, during his short stay in the Austrian town of Linz, on the way home from Vienna to Salzburg. The symphony was written in an impressive span of only four days to accommodate a local concert. The premier took place on November 4 and premiered in Vienna the year after. The introduction of trumpets and drums in the second movement is an unusual feature of the piece. The closing Presto is provided with some contrapuntal passages to contrast the homophonic texture.</desc>
    <date>1991</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306063300 +0100" stop="20260306064400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Saint-Saëns - Intro and Rondo Capriccioso, Op. 28</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Waldbühne, Berlin. The Waldbühne in Berlin, one of the most appealing outdoor amphitheatres on the European continent, is the home of the Berliner Philharmoniker's summer concerts. With over 22.000 in attendance, they are some of the most popular classical music concerts in the world. This year the outstanding orchestra under the baton of Neeme Järvi take us on a trip to Arabian "Thousand and One Nights", with soloist Janine Jansen, a rising star who quickly gained the reputation of one of the foremost young violinists on the international concert stages. On the program are Rimsky-Korsakov's Scheherazade, Symphonic Suite, op. 35, Grieg's 'Peer Gynt' Suite No.1, op. 46, excerpts from Nielsen's Aladdin Suite for Orchestra op. 34, Saint-Saëns's Introduction und Rondo capriccioso and "Meditation" from 'Thais' by Massenet.</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306064400 +0100" stop="20260306081000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Handel - Messiah, HWV 56</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Oude Kerk, Ermelo, The Netherlands. The Messiah (HWV 56) by Georg Frederich Handel, also known as "A New Sacred Oratorio", tells the life and suffering of Christ: a story of passion, fire, and sacrifice. This is one of Handel's best-known works, which took only three weeks to compose this oratorio and its famous "Hallelujah". The work has immense popularity since its premiere in Dublin in 1742, and is often presented at Easter. This performance of the Dutch ensemble Ribattuta Musica under the direction of conductor Dick Duijst was filmed in the grand church of the city of Ermelo, the Netherlands, in 2016. The soloists are Elvire Beekhuizen (soprano), Rosina Fabius (viola), Oscar Verhaar (counter-tenor) Satriya Krisna (tenor), and Hans Voschezang (bass). Ribattuta Musica is a professional ensemble that delivers authentic performances based on current musical practices at the time of the composers.</desc>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306081000 +0100" stop="20260306083300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2021 - Semi-finals: Debussy, Haydn a. o</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Het Noordbrabants Museum, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Soprano Isabel Weller (Germany, 1994) and pianist Yuriko Watanabe (Japan, 1994) perform Claude Debussy's Nuit d'étoiles, L. 2, and Mandoline, L. 43; Joseph Haydn's Piercing eyes, Hob. XXVIa, No. 35; 'Die Mainacht' from Johannes Brahms's Vier Gesänge, Op. 43; 'Pieta' from Paul Hindemith's Das Marienleben, Op. 27; Bart Visman's Vermeer's Gold; and 'Lied vom Winde' from Hugo Wolf's Mörike-Lieder, during the semi-finals of the International Vocal Competition 2021 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Het Noordbrabants Museum in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306083300 +0100" stop="20260306091400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">The Pianists Keys</title>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306091400 +0100" stop="20260306094100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Liszt - Sonata in B minor S.178</title>
    <desc lang="pl">TivoliVredenburg, Utrecht, The Netherlands. Works: Die Lorelei, S532, Sonata in B minor, S178. Pianist Mariam Batsashvili studied successively at the E. Mikeladze Central Music School in Tbilisi with Natalia Natsvlishvili and at the Hochschule für Musik Franz Liszt in Weimar with Grigory Gruzman. She won prizes from various competitions such as the First Prize at the International Franz Liszt Competition for Young Pianists in Weimar in 2011 and Second Prize at the María Herrero International Piano Competition in Granada in 2012. Aside from her native country Georgia, Mariam Batsashvili has performed in such countries as Germany, France, Spain, Italy, Russia, Israel, South Africa and China, both in recitals and with orchestras. She was a soloist with the Erfurt Philharmonisches Orchester and with the Cape Town Philharmonic Orchestra on numerous occasions.</desc>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306094100 +0100" stop="20260306100000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306100000 +0100" stop="20260306113400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mahler - Symphony No. 8</title>
    <desc lang="pl">DR Koncerthuset, Kopenhagen, Denmark. Fabio Luisi conducts the Danish National Symphony Orchestra in a performance of Gustav Mahler's Symphony No. 8. The work is one of the largest-scale choral works in the classical concert repertoire and is frequently called the "Symphony of a Thousand." The work was composed at Mahler's Maiernigg villa in southern Austria in the summer of 1906 and is the last work which was premiered in Mahler's lifetime. Soloists include Ricarda Merbeth (soprano), Henriette Bonde-Hansen (soprano), Sofia Fomini (soprano), Marianne Beate Kielland (alto), Olesya Petrova (alto), Stefan Vinke (tenor), Russel Braun (baritone), and Günther Groissböck (bass). Among the participating choirs are the Danish National Concert Choir, MDR Leipzig Radio Choir and Copenhagen Royal Chapel Choir. Recorded at the DR Koncerthuset in Copenhagen, Denmark, in 2017.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306113400 +0100" stop="20260306124200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Gara Garayev : Autumn Sonatas</title>
    <desc lang="pl">La Grange au Lac, Évian, France. Pianist Vadim Repin and Violist Murad Hüseynov perform Gara Garayev's Violin Sonata and 24 Preludes for Piano. Recorded at La Grange au Lac. Written and directed by Juliette Swierczewski and recorded at La Grange au Lac. Although Garayev is a 20th century composer, his music nonetheless carries allusions to romantic music. Murad, the main actor, will represent one of those characters carried by solitude that can be found in the romantic paintings of Friedrich. The overall atmosphere of the musical program is rather melancholic, tending either towards a certain musical lightness, or, on the contrary, towards drama. The production is a cinematographic accompaniment of the music and its performers.</desc>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306124200 +0100" stop="20260306130200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">England, my England - 2</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Utrecht, Netherlands. From August 28 to September 6, 2015, the Early Music Festival Utrecht was all about 'England, my England'. In line with this theme, presenter Lex Bohlmeijer takes the viewer on an intriguing journey through the England of the Middle Ages, Renaissance and Baroque, and relates this to the city of Utrecht. In episode 2 of this two-part documentary, René de Kam (Heritage Municipality of Utrecht) delves deeper into the Anglican past of the city of Utrecht. The viewer is introduced to festival artists Benjamin Bagby, Skip Sempé, and The Newcastle Kingsmen, who dance their traditional folk "Rapper Sword Dance" during the festival's pub sessions.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306130200 +0100" stop="20260306133500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mexican Concert - Part 2</title>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306133500 +0100" stop="20260306140200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Glass - Double Concerto for Two Pianos</title>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306140200 +0100" stop="20260306153200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">The Babylon Hotel</title>
    <desc lang="pl">DR Koncerthuset, Copenhagen, Denmark. One night only! Welcome to the spectacular and decadent world of The Babylon Hotel, where music pours out of every crevice like bubbling champagne. In this concert, the upper class meets the underworld in a melting pot of euphoria and extravagance, nostalgia and pleasure with a carefree sinfulness only seen in the exuberant nightlife of the 1920s around the world. The concert features iconic music from movies and series, such as The Great Gatsby, Burlesque, and Babylon Berlin. The music is performed by the Danish National Symphony Orchestra and DR Big Band under the direction of Miho Hazama. The concert also features the Moka Efti Orchestra, and singers Madame le Pustra, Emma Smith, Mademoiselle Karen, Jakob Munch, and Nikko Weidemann, as well as dancers of Sweet Burlesque. This performance was recorded at the DR Koncerthuset in Copenhagen, Denmark, in May 2023.</desc>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306153200 +0100" stop="20260306163600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bruckner - Symphony No. 7</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Muziekgebouw, Eindhoven, The Netherlands. In a 2019 performance from the Muziekgebouw in Eindhoven, Hartmut Haenchen conducts the philharmonie zuidnederland for this performance of Anton Bruckner's Symphony No. 7. The German-born conductor, who became a Dutch citizen through naturalisation, was chief conductor at the Dutch National Opera, the Netherlands Philharmonic Orchestra, and the Netherlands Chamber Orchestra before he was finally knighted for his services to the Dutch music landscape. The majestic opening theme of the first movement of Anton Bruckner's Symphony No. 7 foreshadows a momentous work, lasting over 20 minutes. The doubt and turmoil felt throughout the Adagio, the second movement, are supposedly Bruckner's response to the news of the death of his idol, Richard Wagner. Bruckner's use of Wagner tubas and double bass tubas creates an even more solemn and grandiose air within the Adagio. Trumpet signals refer to crowing cockerels as they interrupt the grim and clamorous Scherzo. In the Finale, Bruckner employs a persistent rhythmic pulse that starts softly yet builds up towards the explosive final bars.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306163600 +0100" stop="20260306174900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Brahms Tragic Overture &amp; Mahler Symphony No. 1</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino, Florence, Italy. The Maggio Musicale Fiorentino (Florence Musical May) is Italy's oldest opera and arts festival. It was founded in 1933 with the aim of presenting contemporary and forgotten operas. Over the years, the scope widened, and orchestral concerts have long been an integral part of the festival. As part of the festival's 2021 edition, maestro Daniel Harding leads the Orchestra del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in a wonderful concert program featuring Johannes Brahms's Tragic Overture in D minor, Op. 81, and Gustav Mahler's Symphony No. 1 in D major, 'Titan'. Brahms composed his concert overture during the summer of 1880. With its dark and tumultuous character, it could be regarded as the serious counterpart of his more joyful Academic Festival Overture, Op. 80. Mahler completed his first symphony eight years later, in 1888. Originally a five-movement piece, the composer discarded the second movement 'Blumine' some years later, resulting in the final four-movement version we know today. This performance was recorded at Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in Florence, Italy, in 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306174900 +0100" stop="20260306180200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Schubert - Rondo D. 951</title>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306180200 +0100" stop="20260306183800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 5 in C minor, Op. 67</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Opéra de Dijon, France. Les Dissonances is a collective of artists founded by violinist David Grimal in 2004. The conductorless ensemble consists of musicians from the most prestigious European orchestras, international soloists, and young talents. In this performance, Les Dissonances perform Ludwig van Beethoven's Symphony No. 5 in C minor, Op. 67. Beethoven composed Symphony No. 5 between 1804 and 1808, completing the work at nearly the same time as his Symphony No. 6, 'Pastorale'. Both symphonies premiered as part of an all-Beethoven program at the same concert on December 22, 1808. Symphony No. 5 has become one of the best-known compositions in classical music. It opens with the famous four-note motif, often interpreted as the musical manifestation of 'fate knocking at the door'. This rhythmic figure returns in various guises in the other three movements of the symphony. The second movement consists of a set of lyrical variations on two themes. The third movement begins gently, but leads to a blasting horn section presenting a theme that features the rhythmic pattern of the four-note motif. The movement leads uninterrupted to the fourth movement that features a triumphant finale ending in C major. This performance was recorded at Philharmonie de Paris, France, in 2015.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306183800 +0100" stop="20260306202300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Symphony No. 3, in D minor</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Sala Nezahualcóyotl, Mexico City, Mexico. Mahler's Third Symphony, composed between 1895 and 1896, is an expansive, programmatic work that explores themes of nature, humanity, and spiritual ascent. It features a massive orchestra, a female choir, a children's choir, and a mezzo-soprano soloist, creating a vast soundscape depicting everything from nature's beauty to deeper philosophical questions about existence. The symphony is structured in six movements, moving from the "awakening of nature" to a spiritual conclusion, inspired by Nietzsche and folk poetry.</desc>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306202300 +0100" stop="20260306210100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</title>
    <desc lang="pl">TivoliVredenburg, Utrecht, The Netherlands. Yonghwan Jeong (1991, South Korea) performs Harmonies poétiques et réligieuses, No. 7 Funérailles, S173/7 and Grandes Études de Paganini, S141 during semi-final I (transcription) of the 11th International Franz Liszt Piano Competition, held in TivoliVredenburg, Utrecht, in 2017. The competition actively presents, develops, and promotes piano talents from around the world. In doing so, it has become one of the prominent gateways to the international professional classical music scene for young musicians. The International Franz Liszt Piano Competition was founded in 1986 in the Netherlands and has since built a reputation as one of the world's most prestigious piano competitions.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306210100 +0100" stop="20260306223300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Verdi - Messa da Requiem</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Parco Ducale di Parma, Italy. Roberto Abbado conducts the Filarmonica Arturo Toscanini, the Coro del Teatro Regio di Parma, and four vocal soloists in an outstanding performance of Giuseppe Verdi's Messa da Requiem, recorded at the Parco Ducale di Parma, Italy as part of Festival Verdi 2020. The soloists are soprano Eleonora Buratto, mezzosoprano Anita Rachvelishvili, tenor Giorgio Berrugi, and bass Roberto Tagliavini. When his fellow composer Gioachino Rossini died in 1868, Verdi proposed to compose a 'Messa per Rossini' in his honor, to be written by himself and several other Italian composers. Verdi wrote the concluding movement, 'Libera me'. When the premiere was cancelled, the project lay dormant. When Italian poet Alessandro Manzoni passed away a few years later, Verdi revisited his plan to compose a requiem - this time in honor of the poet he so greatly admired. As an opera composer, Verdi knew better than anyone how to infuse the work with drama, as is evident in the revised version of his 'Libera me'. The famous, powerful 'Dies Irae' especially stands out, depicting the horrors of the Last Judgement.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306223300 +0100" stop="20260306225900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Prokofiev - Peter and the Wolf</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Auditorio Nacional, Mexico City. Mexican conductor Carlos Miguel Prieto leads the Orquesta Sinfónica de Minería in a performance of Sergei Prokofiev's Peter and the Wolf, Op. 67. Written in 1936, Peter and the Wolf is a short, narrated orchestral suite, telling the story of a brave boy named Peter, who lives with his grandfather on the edge of a forest. With the help of his animal friends, Peter outsmarts a villainous wolf and captures it, eventually leading it to the zoo. Maestro Prieto gives an introduction to the different parts of the suite. In each part, each character is represented by a different instrument or instrument section, offering a vivid introduction to the orchestra's instrumental families. This performance was recorded at Auditorio Nacional in Mexico City, in 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306225900 +0100" stop="20260307000000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Playing Portraits</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Galleria Nazionale d'Arte Moderna, Rome. The trio composed of Alessandro Carbonare (clarinet), Elisa Eleonora Papandrea (violin) and Monaldo Braconi (piano) performs regularly in Italy's concert halls and abroad. Playing Portraits showcases the trio's appearances in various places, including USA, Russia and Europe, as they perform works by composers such as George Gershwin, Igor Stravinsky, Francis Poulenc, Anton Guilio Priolo, and Reiner Kuttenberger. This program was recorded by Pietro Tagliaferri at the Salle Belle Epoque in the National Gallery of Modern Art in Rome.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307000000 +0100" stop="20260307015600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Fidelio, Op. 72</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Theater St. Gallen, Switzerland. Fidelio (originally titled "Leonore, oder Der Triumph der ehelichen Liebe," which translates to "Leonore, or the Triumph of Marital Love"), Op. 72, is Ludwig van Beethoven's only opera. This 2018 opera film from the Swiss Theater St. Gallen is based on Jan Schmidt-Garre's highly acclaimed stage production of Beethoven's Fidelio. Otto Tausk conducts the Sinfonieorchester and choir of St. Gallen, as well as many wonderful soloists in a beautifully designed set by Nikolaus Webern. The producers carefully filmed and edited several performances, and by using additional footage of starring soloist Jacquelyn Wagner as Leonore, the captivating stage production is enhanced and transformed into a unique cinematic experience.</desc>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>12</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307015600 +0100" stop="20260307034600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Festive Mozart Concert from Salzburg</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Salzburg Festival. This performance was recorded during Mozart Week on January 27, 2006 in Salzburg, Austria, at the Großes Festspielhaus (Large Festival House) in celebration of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's 250th birthday. Under conductor Riccardo Muti, it features Thomas Hampson (baritone), Mitsuko Uchida (piano), Gidon Kremer (violin), Yuri Bashmet (viola), Wiener Singverein, and Wiener Philharmoniker. Pieces include Piano Concerto No. 25 in C major, Sinfonia concertante in E-flat major, K. 364, arias and scenes from Cosi fan tutte, Le nozze di Figaro, The Magic Flute and Symphony No. 35 in D major, K. 385 ("Haffner").</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307034600 +0100" stop="20260307041100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Modena - The Belcanto School</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307041100 +0100" stop="20260307050500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Rachmaninoff: Piano Concerto No. 3,Op 30</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Avery Fisher Hall, New York City, USA. The legendary pianist Vladimir Horowitz (1903-1989) won his first praise on his interpretation of Rachmaninoff's Third Piano Concerto from the composer himself. When Rachmaninoff heard the young Kiev-born pianist play his work shortly after Horowitz's arrival in New York in 1928, he exclaimed: "He swallowed it whole." Fifty years later, on September 24, 1978, Horowitz electrified his audience once again with this monumental work. Accompanied by the New York Philharmonic under Zubin Mehta, he gave a special performance of this work as part of the celebrations honoring his U.S. debut 50 years earlier. His unforgettable account was recorded live on video and broadcast simultaneously throughout the United States. It was the last time Horowitz played the Third in his lifetime. The work itself, reverently called "Rach 3" by pianists brave enough to tackle its monstrous technical challenges, achieved international celebrity of a different kind in recent years.</desc>
    <date>1978</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307050500 +0100" stop="20260307053400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2021 - Final: Diepenbrock, Fauré a. o</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Verkadefabriek, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Tenor Zhuohan Sun (China, 1993) and pianist Sara Pavlovic (Serbia, 1996) perform 'Wanderlied' from Robert Schumann's Kerner-Lieder, Op. 35; 'Der Abend kommt gezogen' from Alphons Diepenbrock's Drie ballades, Op. 1; Gabriel Fauré's Prison, Op. 83, No. 1; 'Ganymed' from Hugo Wolf's Goethe-Lieder; Franz Schubert's Nacht und Träume, D. 827; Zaiyi Lu's The bridge in my homeland; 'Mit Myrten und Rosen' from Schumann's Liederkreis, Op. 24; 'C' from Francis Poulenc's Deux poemes de Louis Aragon, FP 122; and 'Scheiden und Meiden' from Gustav Mahler's Lieder und Gesänge aus der Jugendzeit, during the final round of the International Vocal Competition 2021 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at De Verkadefabriek in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307053400 +0100" stop="20260307060000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307060000 +0100" stop="20260307070000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Baroque Christmas Concert</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Freiburg Cathedral, Germany. This splendid Christmas concert was recorded live from the Freiburg Cathedral in 1999. It features soprano Barbara Bonney, recognized worldwide for the clarity of her voice and the precision of her diction, and the baritone Matthias Goerne, one of the most promising singers of his generation. Accompanied by the Baroque Orchestra of Freiburg and the German Brass, they perform pieces from Bach's Christmas Oratorio (BWV 248), Mozart's Mass in C minor (KV 427), and Handel's Messiah.</desc>
    <date>1999</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307070000 +0100" stop="20260307071100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - Brandenburg Concerto No. 3</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Hall of Mirrors, Castle of Köthen, Germany. J. S. Bach's six Brandenburg Concerto's belong to his best-known works. The composer wrote these concertos between 1711 and 1720 and dedicated them in 1721 to Christian Ludwig, Margrave of Brandenburg. In celebration of the pieces' 300th anniversary, Czech harpsichordist and conductor Václav Luks and the renowned Baroque ensemble Collegium 1704 recorded all six Brandenburg Concertos on historical instruments in 2021. The concertos are based on the Italian concerto grosso form, in which a group of solo instruments is set against a large ensemble. Bach's Brandenburg Concertos feature remarkable combinations of solo instruments and virtuoso solos. In this performance at the Hall of Mirrors in the Köthen Castle, Germany, Luks and his Collegium 1704 present Bach's Brandenburg Concerto No. 3 in G major, BWV 1048. This concerto was composed for three violins, three violas, three cellos, and basso continuo. Remarkable is the concerto's form: the two fast movements are separated by an Adagio consisting of a single measure of just two chords.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307071100 +0100" stop="20260307090100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Haydn - The Creation</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Church of Jesuits, Lucerne, Switzerland. German conductor Peter Schreier conducts the Scottish Chamber Orchestra, the Luzerner Festwochenchor, and three vocal soloists in a performance of Joseph Haydn's The Creation ('Die Schöpfung'), Hob. XXI:2. The vocal soloists are soprano Edith Mathis, tenor Christoph Prégardien, and bass René Pape. Completed in 1798, Haydn's magnificent oratorio depicts the creation of the world as described in the Bible's Book of Genesis. Its libretto draws from Genesis, the Psalms, and John Milton's epic poem Paradise Lost, and was prepared by the composer's patron Gottfried van Swieten. The work is structured in three parts. The first four days of creation make up part one, dealing with the creation of the earth, its flora, and the celestial objects. The fifth and sixth day of creation form part two, dealing with the creation of animals and humankind. The third part focuses on Adam and Eve in the Garden of Eden. This performance was recorded at the church of Jesuits in Lucerne, Switzerland, in 1992.</desc>
    <date>1992</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307090100 +0100" stop="20260307092200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2021 - Semi-finals: Schubert, Wolf a. o</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Het Noordbrabants Museum, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Soprano Heidi Baumgartner (Austria, 1998) and pianist Asuka Tagami (Japan, 1991) perform Franz Schubert's Suleika I, Op. 14 No. 1, D. 720; 'Er ist's' from Hugo Wolf's Mörike-Lieder; Bart Visman's Vermeer's Gold; 'Sua katselen' (Looking at you) from Kaija Saariaho's Leino-Laulut (Leino songs); and 'Pantomime' and 'Apparition' from Claude Debussy's Quatre chansons de jeunesse, during the semi-finals of the International Vocal Competition 2021 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Het Noordbrabants Museum in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307092200 +0100" stop="20260307093400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Music of Naples</title>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307093400 +0100" stop="20260307094500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Shostakovich - Concertino for two pianos</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Château de Chantilly, France. On the occasion of her 80th birthday, Argentinian pianist Martha Argerich explored repertoire for piano and violin in this wonderful concert, recorded at Château de Chantilly, France. The 'Grande Dame' of the piano is joined by various renowned artists, including pianists Evgeny Kissin, Theodosia Ntokou, and Cristina Marton-Argerich, and violinist Maxim Vengerov. On the program are Dmitri Shostakovich's Concertino for two pianos, Op. 94; Frédéric Chopin's Impromptu No. 3, Op. 51, Polonaise No. 6, Op. 53 "Heroic", and Waltz No. 6, Op. 64 No. 1; Camille Saint-Saëns's Polonaise for two pianos, Op. 77; César Franck's Sonata for violin and piano in A major; and Fritz Kreisler's Liebesleid and Schön Rosmarin. This performance was recorded on June 12, 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307094500 +0100" stop="20260307100100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307100100 +0100" stop="20260307110300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mahler - Symphony No. 4</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Barbican Hall, London, UK. Ukrainian conductor Kirill Karabits leads the London Symphony Orchestra in a stunning performance of Gustav Mahler's Symphony No. 4. The soloist is soprano Lucy Crowe. Mahler's Fourth Symphony opens with the sound of sleighbells and melodies of childlike innocence. But between this deceptively playful opening and the serene finale - a child's vision of Heaven - lies a world of profound emotion and beauty. With soprano Lucy Crowe lending her vocal radiance to this extraordinary finale, the symphony's journey to bliss is complete. This performance was recorded at the Barbican Hall in London, UK, on December 8, 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307110300 +0100" stop="20260307121900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Baroque choral music by Bach, Schütz et al</title>
    <desc lang="pl">St. Thomas Church, Leipzig, Germany. Five-strong vocal ensemble amarcord is joined by an extra alto and two soprano voices for this unusual concert at Leipzig's St. Thomas Church. As amarcordplus, the ensemble presents a program focused on the city of Leipzig, which includes sacred madrigals by Johann Hermann Schein, motets from Heinrich Schütz's collection Geistliche Chor-Music, as well as two motets by the most famous Thomaskantor: Johann Sebastian Bach. Moreover, various sacred works by lesser-known contemporaries Philipp Heinrich Erlebach and mononymous composer Liebhold are performed, in addition to compositions by other members of the Bach family, including Johann Michael Bach and Johann Christoph Bach. This performance was recorded on May 1, 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307121900 +0100" stop="20260307131000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Heavenly Voices - The legacy of Farinelli</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Italy. The documentary 'Heavenly Voices - The Legacy of Farinelli' (2012) tells us the story of the castrato in music - male singers who were castrated at a young age in order to preserve their high vocal range, a cruel practice that was in place mainly in the 17th and 18th centuries. For two centuries, castrati's performances held European audiences spellbound, with successful castrati such as Farinelli ranking among the most influential and highest-earning musicians of those days. Today, roles originally written for castrati are often performed by countertenors. In this documentary, countertenors Max Emanuel Cencić, Philippe Jaroussky, Andreas Scholl, Franco Fagioli, and Jochen Kowalski discuss Baroque-era operatic entertainment. 'Heavenly Voices' is a film by Gino Pennacchi (writer) and Alessandro Scillitani (director).</desc>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307131000 +0100" stop="20260307135100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven-String Quartet No. 14, Op. 131</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Cité de la musique, Paris, France. Renowned French string quartet Quatuor Ébene marked the 250th birth anniversary of Ludwig van Beethoven (1770-1827) with a remarkable project: recording all of the great composer's sixteen string quartets. For five years, violinists Pierre Colombet and Gabriel Le Magadure, violist Marie Chilemme, and cellist Raphaël Merlin immersed themselves in Beethoven's 650 pages of sheet music. Their efforts culminated in the performance of the composer's complete repertoire for string quartet, which covers three decades of Beethoven's musical creativity, during six impressive concerts at Philharmonie de Paris in the autumn of 2020. This program features Quatuor Ébene performing Beethoven's String Quartet No. 14 in C-sharp minor, Op. 131. This concert was recorded at Philharmonie de Paris on December 16, 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307135100 +0100" stop="20260307140300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Smetana - Vltava (The Moldau) from Má vlast</title>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307140300 +0100" stop="20260307154100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IPO 75th Anniversary Gala</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Tel Aviv, Israel. Recorded live in Tel Aviv in 2006, this concert honours the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra on its 70th anniversary. With conductor Zubin Mehta and soloists Pinchas Zukerman and Daniel Barenboim, the celebratory concert encompassed artistry far beyond the usual scope of music performance as it presented the brilliant work of many of the musicians most responsible for, and most appreciative of, the orchestra's rich history. The pianist and conductor Daniel Barenboim maintains a close relationship with the IPO and appears with the orchestra almost every year. Pinchas Zukerman made his debut with the IPO in 1968 and has since continued to appear with the orchestra on a regular basis as a violinist and conductor. On the program are Brahms Piano Concerto No. 1 and the Bruch Violin Concerto No.1 as well as Ravel's Valse, popular and at the same time demanding repertoire - just perfect for a celebration of one of the world's foremost orchestras.</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307154100 +0100" stop="20260307155700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Dvorák - Othello - Concert Overture, Op. 93</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Gewandhaus, Leipzig, Germany. Andris Nelsons, together with his then-wife, the great soprano Kristine Opolais and the Gewandhausorchester Leipzig present a program dedicated to Antonin Dvorák, singing the melodies that the composer hid in all layers of his music with tender, warm, soft colors. Nelsons' tempos remain calm and relaxed, allowing the omnipresent beauty of Dvorák's music to unfold and flood the Gewandhaus. The program opens with Othello, a Concert Overture for Orchestra, Op. 93. Opolais performs "Song to the Moon" from Rusalka, "Songs my Mother Taught Me" from Gypsy Songs, Op. 55/4. This is followed by the Polonaise and 'O, marno, marno to je' from Rusalka and 'Dobrá! Já mu je dám!... Jak je min' from Smetana's opera Dalibor. The concert closes with a performance of Dvorák's Symphony no. 9 in E Minor, Op. 95 ("From the New World"). Recorded at the Gewandhaus, Leipzig in May 2017.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307155700 +0100" stop="20260307172700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Prague Ballet Gala</title>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307172700 +0100" stop="20260307192200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">The 12 Cellists of the Berliner Philharmoniker</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Berliner Philharmonie, Germany. Since 1972 the 12 Cellists of the Berliner Philharmoniker have been a prominent institution in international musical life. Listeners around the world are invariably fascinated by the wide range of the unique and intoxicating timbres that these twelve cellos can produce, whether they are playing classical music, jazz, tango or avant-garde. Their mixture of seriousness and humour, of depth and lightness, appeals to audiences of all ages. Recorded in the Philharmonie Berlin on occasion of the 40th anniversary of the ensemble; soloists: Annette Dasch (soprano), Till Brönner (trumpet).</desc>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307192200 +0100" stop="20260307201200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Celebrate St. Patrick 2020</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Armagh, Ireland. Celebrate St. Patrick 2020 was filmed in March 2020 at Saint Patrick's Cathedral in Armagh, Northern Ireland. Choirs from far and near seized the opportunity to celebrate St. Patrick's Day and perform with local Irish musicians for the congregation of this historic cathedral. The concert merges sacred music, traditional Irish instruments and music from the Irish diaspora. Performances from the highly acclaimed Voices of Ireland, jig dancers, and the rendition of Christ Be Beside Me by the combined choirs are among the many emotional highlights. Readings from the words of St. Patrick and footage of Ireland's glorious landscape make Celebrate Saint Patrick 2020 a feast for the ears and eyes.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307201200 +0100" stop="20260307204300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">PIAM - Semi-final I: Debussy, Chopin and Liszt</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro EDI Barrio's, Milan, Italy. Acclaimed classical music talent scout Antonio Mormone (1930-2017) lives on as the name-giver of the Premio Internazionale Antonio Mormone (PIAM), awarded to the winner of the Italian music competition of the same name. The first edition of this competition, which was held in various venues in Milan from 2019 to 2021, was dedicated to the piano. As part of this competition, Ying Li (China, 1997) performs Claude Debussy's Images, book I; Frédéric Chopin's Nocturne in C-sharp minor, Op. 27 No. 1; and Franz Liszt's Paraphrase from Verdi's 'Rigoletto'. This performance was recorded at Teatro EDI Barrio's in Milan, in February 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307204300 +0100" stop="20260307210400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - Brandenburg Concerto No. 2</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Hall of Mirrors, Castle of Köthen, Germany. J. S. Bach's six Brandenburg Concerto's belong to his best-known works. The composer wrote these concertos between 1711 and 1720 and dedicated them in 1721 to Christian Ludwig, Margrave of Brandenburg. In celebration of the pieces' 300th anniversary, Czech harpsichordist and conductor Václav Luks and the renowned Baroque ensemble Collegium 1704 recorded all six Brandenburg Concertos on historical instruments in 2021. The concertos are based on the Italian concerto grosso form, in which a group of solo instruments is set against a large ensemble. Bach's Brandenburg Concertos feature remarkable combinations of solo instruments and virtuoso solos. In this performance at the Hall of Mirrors in the Köthen Castle, Germany, Luks and his Collegium 1704 present Bach's Brandenburg Concerto No. 2 in F major, BWV 1047. This piece features trumpet, violin, recorder, and oboe solos. Especially outstanding are the high, virtuoso trumpet parts.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307210400 +0100" stop="20260307213500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mahler - Songs on the Death of Children</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Sala Nezahualcóyotl, Mexico City. Mahler's Kindertotenlieder (Songs on the Death of Children) is a deeply personal song cycle for voice and orchestra inspired by Friedrich Rückert's poems about the loss of his children. The work's emotional depth comes from its unflinching portrayal of grief through a powerful juxtaposition of natural imagery and intimate parental pain. Audiences are captivated by the work's profound expression of universal human sorrow and the raw, restrained intensity of Mahler's masterful musical depiction of a parent's pain.</desc>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307213500 +0100" stop="20260307224900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Symphony No. 5</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Sala Nezahualcóyotl, Mexico City, Mexico. Composed between 1901 and 1902, Mahler's Fifth Symphony marked a significant shift in his compositional style, moving away from vocal elements toward a purely symphonic structure. It's a work of immense scope and emotional depth, known for its rich orchestral textures and intricate counterpoint. The symphony is characterized by its innovative use of structure and its exploration of powerful themes, including a profound funeral march, a tender Adagietto for strings and harp, and a vibrant, triumphant finale.</desc>
    <date>2012</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307224900 +0100" stop="20260308000000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Rachmaninoff - Symphony No. 2 in E minor, Op. 27</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro Real, Madrid, Spain. Sir Simon Rattle leads the Berlin Philharmonic in a performance of Sergei Rachmaninoff's Symphony No. 2 in E minor, Op. 27. After the disastrous premiere of the composer's Symphony No. 1 in 1897, Rachmaninoff seriously doubted his ability as a symphonist. Almost a decade later, in October 1906, he started composing his Symphony No. 2. Months of revisions followed. He finished this large orchestral work in the summer of 1907, followed by a highly successful 1908 premiere in St. Petersburg. This performance at the magnificent Teatro Real in Madrid, Spain is part of the Europakonzert 2011.</desc>
    <date>2011</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308000000 +0100" stop="20260308024700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Opernhaus Zürich, Switzerland. Alain Altinoglu conducts the Philharmonia Zürich, Zusatzchor Opernhaus Zürich and SoprAlti der Oper Zürich in a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande, an opera in five acts to the French libretto from Maurice Maeterlinck's play. It was premiered at the in Paris by the Opéra-Comique in 1902. The plot concerns a love triangle; Prince Golaud finds Mélisande, a mysterious young woman. After marrying her he brings her back to the castle of his grandfather, King Arkel, where Mélisande becomes attached to Golaud's younger half-brother Pelléas. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel), Jacques Imbrailo (Pelléas), Kyle Ketelsen (Golaud) and Corinne Winters (Mélisande). Directed by Dmitri Tcherniakov and recorded at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016.</desc>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>12</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308024700 +0100" stop="20260308042500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Waldbühne 2004 - Tchaikovsky night</title>
    <date>2004</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308042500 +0100" stop="20260308044500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">England, my England - 1</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Utrecht, Netherlands. From August 28 to September 6, 2015, the Early Music Festival Utrecht focused on England, my England. On the basis of the festival theme, presenter Lex Bohlmeijer takes the viewer in a two-part documentary on an intriguing journey through England of the Middle Ages, Renaissance and Baroque, and relates this to the city of Utrecht. Episode 1 offers a peek into the inner city churches of Utrecht, visiting the source of inspiration if this year's festival: the English estate Boughton House, where the Duke of Buccleuch shows us around.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308044500 +0100" stop="20260308051800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - Partita for Violin No. 2 (BWV 1004)</title>
    <desc lang="pl">St. Thomas Church, Leipzig, Germany. Celebrated German violinist Isabelle Faust performs J. S. Bach's Partita No. 2 in D minor (BWV 1004). The work is part of the composer's well-known Sonatas and Partitas for Solo Violin (BWV 1001-1006). Partita No. 2 is made up of four dance movements, concluded by its famous Chaconne, a monumental piece within the violin repertoire. In this Chaconne, Bach develops a series of continuous variations from a theme, exploring a complex range of harmonic possibilities. This performance was recorded at St. Thomas Church in Leipzig, Germany, in 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308051800 +0100" stop="20260308054100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Stingray Originals - Seljan Nasibli</title>
    <desc lang="pl">St. Paul's Church Grove Park, London. Azerbaijan-born artist Seljan Nasibli moved to England at an early age, where she was encouraged to take up music. Although Nasibli chose to sing jazz, her Oxford teachers heard an operatic tendency in her voice and advised to train classically. Nasibli completed her studies at The Royal College of Music, where she graduated with a master's degree in Vocal Performance. In this episode of Stingray Originals, Nasibli performs three of Giacomo Puccini's most beautiful arias: 'Signore, ascolta!' and 'Tu, che di gel sei cinta' from the opera Turandot, and 'Quando m'en vo' (Musetta's Waltz) from the opera La boheme.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308054100 +0100" stop="20260308060000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2007</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308060000 +0100" stop="20260308063100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 19, KV 459</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Frankfurt am Main, Germany. When Austria's Emperor Leopold II went to the congress city of Frankfurt to be crowned Holy Roman Emperor in 1790, Mozart hoped to be honored with a commission for a coronation work. The results were disastrous: Antonio Salieri received the commission for a coronation opera and Mozart was asked to write and perform a piano concerto for the coronation ceremonies, a work that was virtually ignored at the time of its creation. In this episode, soloist Radu Lupu performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 19, KV 459 with the Deutsche Kammerphilharmonie, under the baton of David Zinman. The recording took place at the Imperial Hall in Munich.</desc>
    <date>1990</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308063100 +0100" stop="20260308065300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Tchaikovsky - Overture-Fantasy Romeo and Juliet</title>
    <desc lang="pl">De Doelen, Rotterdam. Conrad van Alphen conducts Sinfonia Rotterdam in a performance of Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky's Overture-Fantasy "Romeo and Juliet". Van Alphen founded Sinfonia Rotterdam in 2000. Under his passionate leadership, this orchestra has developed into one of the Netherland's best-known orchestras. Tchaikovsky based his composition on Shakespeare's famous play "Romeo and Juliet". After finishing a first version of Romeo and Juliet in 1870, Tchaikovsky rewrote sections of the composition twice, completing the third and final version ten years later. The Overture-Fantasy opens with a slow introduction, primarily led by the clarinets and bassoons. The composition is dominated by its famous love theme, representing the love between Romeo and Juliet. This beautiful theme is introduced in the first half of the piece, played by the English horn and violas, and recurs in different sections of the composition. At the end, the love theme is heard in minor mode, which emphasized the tragic element of the story of the two lovers.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308065300 +0100" stop="20260308080700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - Partitas for Solo Violin (BWV 1001-1006)</title>
    <desc lang="pl">St. Nikolaus Church, Vienna, Austria. Gidon Kremer's return to J. S. Bach's partitas is a major event. Kremer's first recording of these works was released almost a quarter of a century ago. In this recording from 2006, Kremer once again takes on the greatest challenge for any violinist: Bach's magnificent "Sonatas and Partitas for Solo Violin" (BWV 1001-1006), which Kremer himself calls the "Himalayas" of violin music. With these pieces, Bach firmly established the technical capability of the violin as a solo instrument. The partitas served as archetypes for solo violin pieces by later generations of composers. This rendition of the collection displays Kremer's very personal sense of spontaneity and a readiness to take risks. Yet it is also marked by the structural awareness of an exceptional musician who, in a unique way, does justice both to the polyphonic wealth of the compositions and to their juxtaposition of dance elements and reflective profoundness.</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308080700 +0100" stop="20260308083700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2019 - Final: Schubert, Wolf et al</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Theater aan de Parade, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Soprano Erika Baikoff (United States, 1994) and pianist Gary Beecher (Ireland, 1993) perform Franz Schubert's 'Suleika I, Was bedeutet die Bewegung', Op. 14, No. 1 (D. 720); Die Blumensprache, Op. 173, No. 5 (D. 519); and, Die Gebüsche, D. 646; 'Lied vom Winde' and 'Der Knabe und das Immlein' from Hugo Wolf's Mörike-Lieder; 'Fleur jetée' from Gabriel Fauré's Quatre melodies, Op. 39; 'C' from Francis Poulenc's Deux poemes de Louis Aragon, FP 122; 'Les lilas qui avaient fleuri' from Lili Boulanger's Clairieres dans le ciel; Johanna Bordewijk-Roepman's 'Oranje may-lied'; and, 'Eti letniye nochi' (These summer nights) from Sergei Rachmaninoff's Twelve romances, Op. 14, during the final round of the International Vocal Competition 2019 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Theater aan de Parade in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308083700 +0100" stop="20260308092000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Documentary 2017</title>
    <desc lang="pl">TivoliVredenburg, Utrecht, The Netherlands. This short documentary follows the participants of the 11th International Franz Liszt Piano Competition, held in TivoliVredenburg, Utrecht, in 2017. The competition actively presents, develops, and promotes piano talents from around the world. In doing so, it has become one of the prominent gateways to the international professional classical music scene for young musicians. The International Franz Liszt Piano Competition was founded in 1986 in the Netherlands and has since built a reputation as one of the world's most prestigious piano competitions.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308092000 +0100" stop="20260308094200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Liszt - Piano Concerto No. 1 in E-flat, S.124</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Charles Bronfman Auditorium, Tel Aviv. Dazzling, virtuosic, and spectacular: no other adjectives are better suited to describe the piano music of Franz Liszt. Enjoy a sparkling performance of Liszt's Piano Concerto No. 1 in E flat major by the incredible piano virtuoso Russian Daniil Trifonov, with Kent Nagano conducting the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra. As an encore, Trifonov performs Reflets dans l'eau from Debussy's Images. The orchestra closes this concert with a rendition of Mahler's Symphony No. 7. Recorded at the Charles Bronfman Auditorium, Tel Aviv, in 2014.</desc>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308094200 +0100" stop="20260308100100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308100100 +0100" stop="20260308104000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Works by Kindermann, Fischer, and Baal</title>
    <desc lang="pl">St. Gertrude's Chapel, Utrecht, the Netherlands. Every year in late August, the renowned Early Music Festival takes place in the Dutch city of Utrecht. It is the world's largest festival focused on early music, attracting an audience of over 70 thousand visitors. Due to the corona pandemic, the 2020 edition of the festival took place in an alternative form, offering an alternative program that included live concerts as well as daily livestreams of concerts and archive recordings. As part of this festival edition, Antoinette Lohmann (violin, viola and violino piccolo) and Jörn Boysen (harpsichord) perform a number of rarely performed works from the archives of the Italian musical family Di Martinelli and the Kromeríz collection. On the program are German baroque compositions of Johann Erasmus Kindermann, Johann Fischer, Johann Baal, and others. This concert was recorded at St. Gertrude's Chapel in Utrecht on August 27, 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308104000 +0100" stop="20260308113900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Pierre Boulez and the Lucerne Festival Academy</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Lucerne Festival. For over six decades, Pierre Boulez had a greater influence on the development of contemporary music than anyone else. Already in his younger days, he gained a reputation as a doughty champion of the avant-garde. With his compositions, interpretations and ideas, he indelibly shaped the international music scene - not only as a composer and conductor, but also as a music philosopher and teacher. This documentary by Gunter Atteln and Angelika Stiehler pays tribute to him on the occasion of his 85th birthday on March 26, 2010. For the previous five summers, Pierre Boulez and highly gifted young musicians from all over the world had converged for intensive rehearsal weeks. Over this period, they learned from the maestro and one another, discussing and playing selected compositions. Subsequently, they presented the fruits of their labour in a number of outstanding concerts. To convey the fascination for contemporary music, this documentary captures the perspectives of Pierre Boulez and the young conductors, composers, and musicians involved. Their infectious enthusiasm gives viewers an emotional access to the world of new music.</desc>
    <date>2010</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308113900 +0100" stop="20260308123700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mahler - Symphony No. 1</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Gasteig, Munich, Germany. Jean Paul's novel 'Titan', in which an artistically gifted young man, driven by his failure to find his way in society, eventually commits suicide in despair, inspired Gustav Mahler to compose his Symphony No. 1. The work did not come easily to Mahler: he composed it between 1887 and 1888 when he, in his twenties, was working as a conductor at the Oper Leipzig. The first version of the work was considered as a symphonic poem in two parts, as its titles told a specific musical story. This original version premiered in Budapest in 1898, but it did not go down well. Mahler decided to revise his work: he left out the expressionist titles and cut the second part (Blumine). This results in a wonderful symphony, full of musical references. The opening part quotes one of Mahler's earlier compositions (Ging heut' morgens übers Feld from Lieder eines Fahrenden Gesellen), the second movement is an Austrian ländler (a folk dance), and the third part refers to a very well-known melody: 'Brother John'. All in all, this Symphony No. 1 marks an incredible achievement for a composer this young.</desc>
    <date>2008</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308123700 +0100" stop="20260308133300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">PIAM - Semi-final: Franck, Ravel and Prokofiev</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Auditorium Giorgio Gaber, Milan, Italy. Acclaimed classical music talent scout Antonio Mormone (1930-2017) lives on as the name-giver of the Premio Internazionale Antonio Mormone (PIAM), awarded to the winner of the Italian music competition of the same name. The first edition of this competition, which was held in various venues in Milan from 2019 to 2021, was dedicated to the piano. As part of this competition, Piotr Pawlak (Poland, 1998) performs César Franck's Prelude, Chorale and Fugue in B minor; Maurice Ravel's Pavane pour une infant défunte; and Sergei Prokofiev's Sonata No. 4 in C minor, Op. 29. As an encore, Pawlak plays J. S. Bach's Prelude and Fugue in C major, BWV 846; the final fugue from Leopold Godowsky's Passacaglia in B minor; and Frédéric Chopin's Etude in C-sharp minor, Op. 10 No. 4. This performance was recorded at Auditorium Giorgio Gaber in Milan, in November 2019.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308133300 +0100" stop="20260308140000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2021 - Semi-finals: Ives, Brahms a. o</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Het Noordbrabants Museum, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Bass-baritone Matthias Hoffmann (Austria, 1991) and pianist Lisa Ochsendorf (Germany, 1991) perform 'A. Very pleasant' from Charles Ives's song 'Memories'; 'Nachtwanderer' from Hans Erich Pfitzner's Fünf Lieder, Op. 7; 'Nachts' from Hans Sommer's Zehn Lieder, Op. 9; 'Da unten im Tale' from Johannes Brahms's Deutsche Volkslieder, WoO. 33; Henri Duparc's Chanson triste; Bart Visman's Vermeer's gold; 'La maîtresse volage' from Francis Poulenc's Chansons gaillardes, FP 42; Franz Schubert's Gruppe aus dem Tartarus, Op. 24, No. 1, D. 583; 'Na smert' chizhika' (On the death of a linnet) from Sergei Rachmaninoff's Twelve Romances, Op. 21; and 'Sprich, Scheherazade' from Moritz Eggert's Neue Dichter Lieben, during the semi-finals of the International Vocal Competition 2021 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Het Noordbrabants Museum in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308140000 +0100" stop="20260308164100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bizet - Carmen</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Festival St. Margarethen. The wild and breathtaking scenery of Austria's Roman Quarry of St. Margarethen provides an ideal and unique backdrop for this live and colourful open-air performance of Georges Bizet's opera Carmen (1875). With over 400 participants, this opulent staging of Bizet's famous opera - one of the most popular works in the genre's history - proves a feast for all the senses. Austria's Opera Festival St. Margarethen, one of Europe's most important open-air festivals, is attended by about 220, 000 opera lovers every year. The Brno National Theatre Orchestra &amp; Chorus is led by conductor Ernst Märzendorfer. Soloists are Nadia Krasteva, Russi Nikov and Alexandr Antonenko.</desc>
    <date>2005</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>16</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308164100 +0100" stop="20260308181900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - String Quartets No. 4, 5 &amp; 12</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Cité de la musique, Paris, France. Renowned French string quartet Quatuor Ébene marked the 250th birth anniversary of Ludwig van Beethoven (1770-1827) with a remarkable project: recording all of the great composer's sixteen string quartets. For five years, violinists Pierre Colombet and Gabriel Le Magadure, violist Marie Chilemme, and cellist Raphaël Merlin immersed themselves in Beethoven's 650 pages of sheet music. Their efforts culminated in the performance of the composer's complete repertoire for string quartet, which covers three decades of Beethoven's musical creativity, during six impressive concerts at Philharmonie de Paris in the autumn of 2020. Quatuor Ébene explored every facet of Beethoven's string quartet repertoire: from the youthful Opus 18 string quartets to the Razumovsky, Harp, and Serioso quartets (Opus 59, 74, and 95) from his middle period, and finally, the depth of his late quartets (Opus 127 to 135). This program features Quatuor Ébene performing Beethoven's String Quartet No. 5 in A major, Op. 18, No. 5; String Quartet No. 4 in C minor, Op. 18, No. 4; and String Quartet No. 12 in E-flat major, Op. 127. This concert was recorded at Philharmonie de Paris on December 17, 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308181900 +0100" stop="20260308183700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Ravel - Mother Goose Suite</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Snape Maltings Concert Hall, Snape Bridge, UK. Marin Alsop conducts the Britten-Pears Orchestra in a performance of Maurice Ravel's 'Ma mere l'Oye' (Mother Goose). This performance took place at Snape Maltings Concert Hall, Snape Bridge in the UK in 2017. This five-part orchestral suite was originally as a piano duet in 1910, but the composer orchestrated the work the year after. Ravel originally composed the work as a piano duet for the two children of Polish sculptor Gobeski and dedicated the work for four hands to the children.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308183700 +0100" stop="20260308185100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Piano Sonata No. 5, KV 283</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Villa Contarini, Padova, Italy. Italian pianist Roberto Prosseda (1975) performs Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's Piano Sonata No. 5, KV. 283. Prosseda is particularly noted for his performances of newly discovered works by Mendelssohn and has recorded a nine-CD series for Decca of the piano works of Mendelssohn. Since 2012, Prosseda also gives lecture-concerts with the robot pianist TeoTronico, as educational or family concerts, to demonstrate differences between a literal production of music and human interpretation.</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308185100 +0100" stop="20260308194600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">In Rehearsal: Zubin Mehta</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Tel Aviv, Israel. Indian conductor Zubin Mehta (1936) became Music Director of the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra (IPO) in 1977 and was appointed Music Director for Life in 1981. On July 18, 1996, Mehta led the IPO in its first-ever performance of Richard Strauss's tone poem Till Eulenspiegels lustige Streiche, Op. 28. Renowned as one of the world's foremost interpreters of the great symphonic repertoire-especially the Romantic works of Anton Bruckner, Gustav Mahler, and Richard Strauss-Mehta had conducted this popular masterpiece many times before. However, this was the first occasion he rehearsed it from the very beginning with the orchestra. This episode of 'In Rehearsal' offers an intimate look at the dialogue between Mehta and the musicians as they explore Strauss's tone poem together.</desc>
    <date>1996</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308194600 +0100" stop="20260308204000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Berlioz - Symphonie Fantastique, Op. 14</title>
    <date>2001</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308204000 +0100" stop="20260308210100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308210100 +0100" stop="20260308222700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mahler - Symphony No. 2, 'Resurrection</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino, Florence, Italy. Maestro Myung-Whun Chung leads the Orchestra and Chorus of the Maggio Musicale Fiorentino, along with two vocal soloists, in this impressive performance of Gustav Mahler's Symphony No. 2 in C minor, 'Resurrection'. Soprano Christiane Karg and alto Claudia Huckle are the soloists. Written between 1888 and 1894, this five-movement symphony is scored for a large orchestra, chorus, and soprano and alto soloists. Mahler explores themes of life, death, and resurrection throughout the symphony. Its first movement resembles a funeral march, while the second, a graceful Ländler, creates a stark contrast with the somber character of the first. The third movement is a Scherzo based on Mahler's musical setting of 'Des Antonius von Padua Fischpredigt' from the collection Des Knaben Wunderhorn. The composer also used another Wunderhorn poem, 'Urlicht' (Primal Light), for the fourth movement, incorporating both text and music, sung by the alto. The chorus makes its entrance in the second part of the fifth and final movement with the 'Resurrection' chorale. This performance was recorded at Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in Florence, Italy, in 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308222700 +0100" stop="20260308234900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Brahms - A German Requiem, Op. 45</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Stift Basilika St. Florian, Austria. In this concert recorded in November 2016 at the magnificent Baroque basilica of Saint Florian, Austria - once the home of Anton Bruckner - the Wiener Singverein, the Cleveland Orchestra and its principal conductor Franz Welser-Möst pare down all traces of bombast wherever emotions could easily run out of control. Brahms' Ein Deutsches Requiem, Op. 45, reaches out to comfort the living through religious texts not traditionally associated with the Requiem Mass. The result is a work of great intensity that speaks to people of all faiths, believers and non-believers alike. The program's two soloists - Hanna-Elisabeth Müller and Simon Keenlyside - are already at home on the world's stages. While the former has carved a career for herself not only as an opera singer but also as a concert artist, the London-born Keenlyside has been building his impressive career around the prestigious guest appearances he has made during the past ten years.</desc>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308234900 +0100" stop="20260309000000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309000000 +0100" stop="20260309015000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Gluck - Iphigénie en Tauride</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Grand Théâtre d'Angers, France. Iphigénie en Tauride (1779) is a four-act tragic opera by German-born composer Christoph Willibald Gluck. Written for the French stage, the work's premiere in 1779 at the Parisian Royal Academy of Music was a great success. Iphigénie en Tauride is one of the composer's 'reform operas', meaning that the music was to follow the drama and its expression. Nicolas-François Guillard's libretto is based on Claude Guimond de La Touche's play of the same name, but ultimately it derives from Euripides's famous ancient Greek drama. Set shortly after the Trojan War, Iphigénie, who was to be sacrificed by her father Agamemnon, is saved and carried off by the goddess Diana to Tauris, where Iphigénie becomes Diana's high priestess. Diego Fasolis conducts the Orchestre National des Pays de la Loire and the Cheur d'Angers Nantes Opéra in this production. Among the soloists are Marie-Adeline Henry (Iphigénie), Charles Rice (Oreste), Sébastien Droy (Pylade), Jean-Luc Ballestra (Thoas), and Élodie Hache (Diane). This performance was recorded at the Grand Théâtre d'Angers, France, in 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>16</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309015000 +0100" stop="20260309035600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - St. John Passion</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Philharmonie Berlin, Germany. Sir Simon Rattle conducts the marvelous Berliner Philharmoniker and performs Johann Sebastian Bach's splendid St. John Passion. The solo voice parts are sung by the renowned soloists Juliane Banse, Michael Chance, Ian Bostridge, Rainer Trost and Thomas Quasthoff. Also joining is the famous RIAS Kammerchor. Bach composed his passion, based on the Gospel of John, during his first year as director of church music in Leipzig. It was first performed on Good Friday in 1724. Highlights of this piece are the opening chorus, the death of Jesus and the closing chorale. The music is full of emotions due to the fragile solo passages and the intense choir parts.</desc>
    <date>2002</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309035600 +0100" stop="20260309041600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">England, my England - 2</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Utrecht, Netherlands. From August 28 to September 6, 2015, the Early Music Festival Utrecht was all about 'England, my England'. In line with this theme, presenter Lex Bohlmeijer takes the viewer on an intriguing journey through the England of the Middle Ages, Renaissance and Baroque, and relates this to the city of Utrecht. In episode 2 of this two-part documentary, René de Kam (Heritage Municipality of Utrecht) delves deeper into the Anglican past of the city of Utrecht. The viewer is introduced to festival artists Benjamin Bagby, Skip Sempé, and The Newcastle Kingsmen, who dance their traditional folk "Rapper Sword Dance" during the festival's pub sessions.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309041600 +0100" stop="20260309050800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 3 in E-flat major, Op. 55</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Opéra Bastille, Paris, France. Swiss conductor Philippe Jordan and the Orchestre de l'Opéra national de Paris recorded all of Ludwig van Beethoven's symphonies in 2014-2015. In this program, Jordan conducts Beethoven's Symphony No. 3 in E-flat major, Op. 55, 'Eroica'. Composed in 1803 and 1804, this symphony is regarded as a major turning point in Beethoven's oeuvre as well as Western music history. Symphony No. 3 is longer in duration than any previous symphony. The customary long introduction is replaced by two powerful chords, followed by the introduction of the main theme by the lower strings. The slow second movement is a Funeral March, followed by a quick Scherzo. The fourth and final movement is dominated by a theme from Beethoven's ballet music for 'The Creatures of Prometheus'. This performance was recorded at Opéra Bastille in Paris, France, in 2014.</desc>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309050800 +0100" stop="20260309053600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2019 - Final: Schubert, Schumann et al</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Theater aan de Parade, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Soprano Harriet Burns (United Kingdom, 1989) and pianist Ian Tindale (United Kingdom, 1990) perform Franz Schubert's Verklärung, D. 59; Clara Schumann's Er ist gekommen in Sturm und Regen, Op. 12, No. 2; 'L'heure exquise' from Reynaldo Hahn's Chansons grises, and 'Le printemps' from Hahn's Douze rondels; 'Herzeleid' from Robert Schumann's Sechs Gesänge, Op. 107; 'Le corbeau et le renard' from André Caplet's Trois fables; Alphons Diepenbrock's Die Liebende schreibt, RC 20; 'Seranilla de la zarzuela' from Judith Weir's A Spanish liederbooklet; Muriel Herbert's Renouncement; and 'Waldmädchen' from Hugo Wolf's Eichendorff-Lieder, during the final round of the International Vocal Competition 2019 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Theater aan de Parade in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309053600 +0100" stop="20260309060000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2007</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309060000 +0100" stop="20260309065900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Rolando Villazón - One Night in Berlin</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Berliner Philharmonie. French-Mexican tenor Rolando Villazón (1972) is accompanied by the Südwestdeutsche Kammerphilharmonie Konstanz in performing a colourful recital from the Berliner Philharmonie. In this concert from 2006, Villazón performs various arias by Italian opera composers like Verdi, Rossini, Donizetti, Cilea and Mascagni. On the program are also some French works by Massenet, like Ô Souverain, ô juge, ô pere from Le Cid and Toute mon âme est la! Pourquoi me réveiller, ô souffle du printemp from 'Werther'. Through his uniquely compelling performances with leading opera houses and orchestras around the world, Villazón established himself as one of the music world's most beloved stars and one of the leading tenors of our day. The Times heralded him as "the most charming of today's divos.</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309065900 +0100" stop="20260309072400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Ravel - Piano Concerto in G major</title>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309072400 +0100" stop="20260309084900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Grieg's Piano Concerto &amp; Beethoven Symphony No. 7</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Concertgebouw Brugge, Belgium. Conductor Jan Latham-Koenig leads the Flanders Symphony Orchestra in this concert recorded at Concertgebouw Brugge, Belgium, on April 21, 2016. The program opens with Felix Mendelssohn's concert overture Die Hebriden, Op. 26 (The Hebrides). During a trip to Scotland, the composer was deeply impressed by the natural splendor of Staffa, an island of the Inner Hebrides, which inspired him to compose his concert overture. Next on the program is Edvard Grieg's Piano Concerto in A minor, Op. 16, featuring Pascal Amoyel as the pianist. It is the composer's only concerto. Grieg composed the work in 1868, drawing inspiration from Norwegian folk music. The program ends with Ludwig van Beethoven's Symphony No. 7 in A major, Op. 92. The work is very popular, especially because of its touching second movement. At the Allegretto's 1813 premiere, the audience demanded an immediate encore.</desc>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309084900 +0100" stop="20260309090500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Telemann - Jesus liegt in letzten Zügen, TWV 1:983</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Alte Oper Frankfurt, Germany. The film Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann is a portrait of a very special vocalist, and of two exceptional composers. When Philippe Jaroussky - whose angelic voice seems almost timeless, not belonging to any one epoque or decade - sings works by Telemann and Bach, it becomes abundantly clear that the sheer emotional force and the purifying power of their music have not diminished over the centuries. The works performed in this film are Telemann's Jesus liegt in letzten Zügen and Sinfonia from Brockes-Passion; Der am Ölberg zagende Jesus, and Bach's Sinfonia from Ich hatte viel Bekümmernis and Ich habe genug.</desc>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309090500 +0100" stop="20260309092900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Modena - The Belcanto School</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309092900 +0100" stop="20260309094300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Schubert - Rondo D. 951</title>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309094300 +0100" stop="20260309100400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309100400 +0100" stop="20260309104600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">The Pianists Keys</title>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309104600 +0100" stop="20260309105800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">CMIM Piano 2024 - Semi-final I: Anthony Ratinov</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Bourgie Hall, Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, Canada. Pianist Anthony Ratinov (USA, 1997) joins the CMIM ensemble, consisting of three principal strings players of the Montreal Symphony Orchestra, in a performance of the first movement, Sostenuto assai - Allegro ma non troppo, of Robert Schumann's Piano Quartet in E-flat major, Op. 47. This performance took place during the chamber music round of the two-part semi-final of the Piano Edition of the Concours musical international de Montréal 2024 (CMIM). It was recorded at the Bourgie Hall of the Montreal Museum of Fine Arts.</desc>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309105800 +0100" stop="20260309113200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Chopin - Piano Concerto No. 2, Op. 21</title>
    <date>2010</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309113200 +0100" stop="20260309130300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Chamber music by Haydn, Chausson &amp; Mendelssohn</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Auditorio Sony, Reina Sofía School of Music, Madrid, Spain. Discover the next generation of chamber music talent from the Reina Sofía School of Music. In the first half of this program, Trio Michelangeli presents two masterpieces: Joseph Haydn's Piano Trio No. 39 in G major, nicknamed 'Gypsy', followed by the romanticism of Ernest Chausson's Piano Trio in G minor. The concert concludes with a performance by the Erinys Quartet of Felix Mendelssohn's inventive String Quartet No. 2 in A minor. This performance was recorded at Auditorio Sony of the Reina Sofía School of Music in Madrid, Spain, on June 7, 2024.</desc>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309130300 +0100" stop="20260309140000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">PIAM - Final: Beethoven, Chopin and Prokofiev</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Sala Verdi, Conservatory of Milan, Italy. Acclaimed classical music talent scout Antonio Mormone (1930-2017) lives on as the name-giver of the Premio Internazionale Antonio Mormone (PIAM), awarded to the winner of the Italian music competition of the same name. The first edition of this competition, which was held in various venues in Milan from 2019 to 2021, was dedicated to the piano. During the competition's final round, Ying Li (China, 1997) performs Ludwig van Beethoven's Sonata No. 28 in A major, Op. 101; Frédéric Chopin's Fantasia in F minor, Op. 49; and Sergei Prokofiev's Sonata No. 7 in B-flat major, Op. 83. This performance was recorded at Sala Verdi of the Conservatory of Milan, in July 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309140000 +0100" stop="20260309153600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Gershwin - Greatest Hits</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Concertgebouw Brugge, Belgium. Belgian conductor Jos van Immerseel leads Anima Eterna Brugge in a concert program dedicated to American composer George Gershwin. The program opens with Gershwin's symphonic suite Catfish Row (arr. Steven D. Bowen) which is based upon music from his famous opera Porgy and Bess (1935). This is followed by the well-known tone poem An American in Paris (1928). After, soprano Claron McFadden joins the orchestra, presenting a selection of Gershwin's classic jazz songs, including 'The man I love' (1924-27), 'I got rhythm' (1930), and 'By Strauss' (1936). She also performs 'My man's gone now' and 'Summertime' from Porgy and Bess. The concert ends with Gershwin's celebrated Rhapsody in Blue, with Bart Van Caenegem as featured pianist. This performance was recorded at Concertgebouw Brugge, Belgium, on March 3, 2017.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309153600 +0100" stop="20260309155300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - Brandenburg Concerto No. 6</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Hall of Mirrors, Castle of Köthen, Germany. J. S. Bach's six Brandenburg Concerto's belong to his best-known works. The composer wrote these concertos between 1711 and 1720 and dedicated them in 1721 to Christian Ludwig, Margrave of Brandenburg. In celebration of the pieces' 300th anniversary, Czech harpsichordist and conductor Václav Luks and the renowned Baroque ensemble Collegium 1704 recorded all six Brandenburg Concertos on historical instruments in 2021. The concertos are based on the Italian concerto grosso form, in which a group of solo instruments is set against a large ensemble. Bach's Brandenburg Concertos feature remarkable combinations of solo instruments and virtuoso solos. In this performance at the Hall of Mirrors in the Köthen Castle, Germany, Luks and his Collegium 1704 present Bach's Brandenburg Concerto No. 6 in B-flat major, BWV 1051. Contrary to the other five concertos, this piece does not include violins, instead offering the floor to the lower strings and the harpsichord.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309155300 +0100" stop="20260309172900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Ice Dance: Sleeping Beauty (2013)</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro Montecasino, Johannesburg, South Africa.. The award-winning Imperial Ice Stars are 26 Olympic, World, European and National Championship skaters, who jointly hold over 250 competition medals, performing theatrical ice dancing on a frozen theatre stage. The Imperial Ice Stars have received five-star praise from critics and standing ovations from audiences at some of the world's most prestigious venues - London's Royal Albert Hall and Sadler's Wells, Singapore's Esplanade Theatre, Montreal's Place des Arts and Cape Town's Artscape. This stunning performance, filmed at the Melbourne Theatre Company in Australia, offers a new look on the secular tale of Sleeping beauty, with the original music of Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky (1840-1893).</desc>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309172900 +0100" stop="20260309190000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Legato - World of the Piano</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Philharmonie, Essen. We live in a "renaissance of the piano", as the New York Times has recently put it. With virtuosic flair and an eagerness to expand the repertoire, a new generation of pianists has revitalized the instrument's appeal. In addition to the usual classics, they perform formerly scorned works or discover neglected composers. Legato is a series dedicated to presenting some of this new movement's most fascinating pianists - their individual approaches, their fresh ideas and their music. Each episode portrays an artist and shows an aspect of the world of the piano. The sum of these portraits provides viewers with an overall picture of the art of the pianist. Montréal native Marc-André Hamelin is internationally renowned for his musical virtuosity and refined pianism. The Times described one of his performances as "ultimate perfection". He plays works by Haydn (Piano sonata in E major), Chopin (Piano sonata No. 3), Debussy ('Préludes', book two), Hamelin (Etude No. 7), as well as two short pieces by Gershwin ('Do, Do, Do' and 'Liza').</desc>
    <date>2007</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309190000 +0100" stop="20260309195900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">A Singalong Christmas</title>
    <desc lang="pl">LSO St Luke's, London, UK. Chorus Director Emeritus Simon Halsey conducts the London Symphony Orchestra (LSO) and Chorus in the festive concert 'A Singalong Christmas'. Joined by soprano Abigail Kelly and bass-baritone Rodney Earl Clarke, the LSO presents a full program of festive works to sing along with. The program includes: Carillon on 'Angelus ad Virginem'; African Noel; Adam Lay Ybounden; Carol of the Crib; Babe of Bethlehem; Shepherd's Hey; The First Nowell; Sir Christmas; Hark! The Herald Angels Sing; Christmas Overture; Tomorrow shall be my dancing day; Shout for Joy!; Sleigh Ride; and O Come, All Ye Faithful. This atmospheric concert was recorded at LSO St. Luke's in London, UK, on October 21, 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309195900 +0100" stop="20260309202600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Schumann - Humoreske, Op. 20</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Italy. After recording all 32 Ludwig van Beethoven piano sonatas to celebrate the composer's 250th birth anniversary, celebrated Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz decided to record solo piano works by Robert Schumann. In this performance, Schwartz performs Humoreske in B-flat major, Op. 20. Schumann composed the work in 1839 and dedicated it to German-Austrian composer Julie von Webenau. The piece's title refers to humor as an emotional state. Schumann took his inspiration from German Romantic writer Jean Paul, who defines humor as "an infinity of contrast", "a setting of the small world beside the great", and where "a kind of laughter results which contains pain and greatness". Humoreske is one continuous piece consisting of contrasting sections. Acclaimed pianist Riccardo Schwartz (1986) has performed as a soloist with many world-renowned conductors, including Gustav Kuhn and Yuri Temirkanov. His acclaimed performances include recitals and concertos for piano and orchestra in many prestigious concert halls.</desc>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309202600 +0100" stop="20260309204900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Violin Concerto No. 3</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Cité de la Musique, Paris. Les Dissonances is a collective of artists founded by violinist David Grimal in 2004. The conductorless ensemble consists of musicians from the most prestigious European orchestras, international soloists, and young talents. In this performance, Les Dissonances play Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's Violin Concerto No. 3 in G major, K. 216. Leading violinist Grimal features as the soloist. With the exception of the first violin concerto, Mozart composed his other four violin concertos in 1775 at a time when he was concertmaster at the Salzburg court. Violin Concerto No. 3 opens with a theme the composer borrowed from the aria 'Aer tranquillo' of his then recent opera Il re pastore. In the beautiful Adagio, the strings are muted and the oboes make way for the flutes, which only sound in the second movement. The finale movement has a dance-like character. This performance was recorded at Cité de la Musique, France, in 2014.</desc>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309204900 +0100" stop="20260309210100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309210100 +0100" stop="20260309230800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Puccini - Tosca</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Easter Festival, Baden-Baden, Germany. For the Easter Festival 2017 in Baden-Baden, Sir Simon Rattle and the Berliner Philharmoniker draw their inspiration from Tosca, the most well-known and most brilliant of all the Puccini operas. And that is deservedly so since Tosca is not merely a work of art, but also a gripping suspense-packed story. The opera premiered in 1900 at the Teatro Costanzi in Rome. The three-act opera is based on an Italian libretto by Luigi Illica and Giuseppe Giacosa. For this performance, Philipp Himmelmann created a spectacular staging that offers a new view of this beloved classic. With Kristine Opolais as Tosca and Marcelo Álvarez as Mario Cavaradossi.</desc>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>16</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309230800 +0100" stop="20260310000000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 8 in F major, Op. 93</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Opéra Bastille, Paris, France. Swiss conductor Philippe Jordan and the Orchestre de l'Opéra national de Paris recorded all of Ludwig van Beethoven's symphonies in 2014-2015. In this program, Jordan conducts Beethoven's Symphony No. 8 in F major, Op. 93. Beethoven wrote the work in 1812 upon completion of his Symphony No. 7. The composer conducted the February 27, 1814 premiere at a concert in Vienna that also included a reprise performance of his Symphony No. 7 and his 15-minute orchestral piece Wellington's Victory, Op. 91. The shortest of Beethoven's nine symphonies, Symphony No. 8 lacks a truly slow movement. Instead it has a second movement, Allegretto scherzando, that features a steady 'ticking' rhythm maintained by the woodwinds throughout the movement. This is thought to be an imitation of the Andante movement of Joseph Haydn's 'Clock' Symphony. Jordan's performance was recorded at Opéra Bastille in Paris, France, in 2015.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310000000 +0100" stop="20260310021200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Verdi - Rigoletto</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino, Florence, Italy. Riccardo Frizza leads the Orchestra and Chorus of the Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in a performance of Giuseppe Verdi's tragic opera Rigoletto (1851). In 1850, Teatro La Fenice commissioned Verdi to compose a new opera. Verdi proposed Victor Hugo's controversial play Le Roi s'amuse to his librettist Francesco Maria Piave. This play, which premiered in 1832 but was banned after only one performance, portrayed the monarchy in its worst vices. However, Verdi was determined to adapt the play to opera and reached a compromise with the censor. The opera revolves around Rigoletto, a hunchbacked jester at the court of the licentious Duke of Mantua. Rigoletto's life is turned upside down when his latest wisecrack starts a vendetta that is far from amusing, leaving him cursed. In this 2021 production, Italian director Davide Livermore follows the story as we know it, but places it in a contemporary setting. Among the soloists are Javier Camarena (Duke of Mantua), Luca Salsi (Rigoletto), Enkeleda Kamani (Gilda), Alessio Cacciamani (Sparafucile), Caterina Piva (Maddalena), and Valentina Coró (Giovanna). This performance was recorded at Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in Florence, Italy, in 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>16</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310021200 +0100" stop="20260310040700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Israel Philharmonic Orchestra: 60th Anniversary</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Mann Auditorium, Tel Aviv. In 1996, the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra celebrated its 60th anniversary with a gala led by maestros Zubin Mehta and Daniel Barenboim. This musical event features world-renowned soloists, including veteran violinist Isaac Stern, up-and-coming musicians Maxim Vengerov and Gil Shaham, as well as Pinchas Zukerman, Shlomo Mintz, and Itzhak Perlman. The evening begins with a moving speech about the early days of the orchestra. The evening's program continues with Bach's Concerto for Two Violins in D minor, BWV1043, Brahms's Symphony No. 2, Halvorsen's Violin, Violoncello and Viola Pass, Mozart's Serenade No. 6, K. 239., Vivaldi's Concerto in B minor for four violins and orchestra, and Weber's Oberon overture.</desc>
    <date>1996</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310040700 +0100" stop="20260310050200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">In Rehearsal: Esa-Pekka Salonen</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Dorothy Chandler Pavilion, Music Center of Los Angeles County, USA. The Finnish composer and conductor Esa-Pekka Salonen (1958) was Music Director of the Los Angeles Philharmonic from 1992 until 2009. Under his dynamic leadership, it was recognized as one of the world's most outstanding orchestras. The exciting musical partnership Salonen established with his musicians was widely acclaimed in the international press. The conductor's lucidity, efficiency, and lack of pretension, promoted a relaxed collaboration between himself and the orchestra, which is particularly evident in the rehearsal process. This 'In Rehearsal' episode features Salonen rehearsing Claude Debussy's Impressionistic orchestral piece La Mer with the Los Angeles Philharmonic at the Dorothy Chandler Pavilion of the Music Center of Los Angeles County. It gives a fascinating insight into Salonen's rapport with his musicians and also into Debussy's masterpiece.</desc>
    <date>1997</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310050200 +0100" stop="20260310053300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 5 in C minor, Op. 67</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310053300 +0100" stop="20260310054500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Telemann - Der am Ölberg zagende Jesus, TWV 1: 364</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Alte Oper Frankfurt, Germany. The film Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann is a portrait of a very special vocalist, and of two exceptional composers. When Philippe Jaroussky - whose angelic voice seems almost timeless, not belonging to any one epoque or decade - sings works by Telemann and Bach, it becomes abundantly clear that the sheer emotional force and the purifying power of their music have not diminished over the centuries. The works performed in this film are Telemann's Jesus liegt in letzten Zügen and Sinfonia from Brockes-Passion; Der am Ölberg zagende Jesus, and Bach's Sinfonia from Ich hatte viel Bekümmernis and Ich habe genug.</desc>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310054500 +0100" stop="20260310060000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310060000 +0100" stop="20260310062600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 6, K 238</title>
    <date>1990</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310062600 +0100" stop="20260310065500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Prokofiev - Violin Concerto No. 2, Op. 63</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Béla Bartók National Concert Hall, Budapest, Hungary. Iván Fischer conducts the Budapest Festival Orchestra in a concert recorded at the Béla Bartók National Concert Hall in Budapest, Hungary in 2015. The concert opens with Sergei Prokofiev's Overture on Hebrew Themes, Op. 34. After this, Thomas Zehetmair stars as solo violinist in Prokofiev Violin Concerto No. 2, Op. 63. The second part of the concert is features music by Igor Stravinsky. On the program is music composed for the ballet 'Jeu de cartes' (1937) and the Firebird Suite, No. 2 (1919). 'Jeu de cartes' is one of Stravinsky's neo-classical works and consists of three parts ('deals'). The Firebird Suite, No. 2 is based on the music from the ballet of the same name, which was written for Sergei Diaghilev's Ballets Russes and premiered in Paris in 1910.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310065500 +0100" stop="20260310075000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Works by Haydn, Mozart and Saint-Saëns</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Basilica di San Pietro, Perugia, Italy. Italian cellist and conductor Enrico Bronzi leads the Orchestra da Camera di Perugia in this intimate concert at the magnificent Basilica di San Pietro in the Italian city of Perugia, recorded on September 27, 2021. Opening the program is a cello performance by Bronzi with the Orchestra da Camera di Peruglia: the Andante cantabile from Joseph Haydn's Symphony No. 13 in D major, Hob. I:13. Then, Italian pianists Linda Di Carlo and Marco Scolastra join the orchestra for a performance of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's Concerto for two pianos and orchestra in E-flat major, K. 365. Next up is Mozart's concert aria "Ch'io mi scordi di ten ... Non temer, amato bene", K. 505, sung by Italian mezzosoprano Marina Comparato. Accompanied by Linda Di Carlo on piano, she closes the concert with the aria "Mon coeur s'ouvre a ta voix" from Camille Saint-Saëns's opera Samson and Delilah.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310075000 +0100" stop="20260310081400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2021 - Semi-finals: Schönberg, Britten a. o</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Het Noordbrabants Museum, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Baritone Arvid Fagerfjäll (Sweden, 1991) and pianist Hikaru Kanki (Japan, 1993) perform Franz Schubert's An mein Herz, D. 860; 'Die Aufgeregten' from Arnold Schönberg's Sechs Lieder, Op. 3; 'A poison tree' from Benjamin Britten's The red cockatoo and other songs; Bart Visman's Vermeer's Gold; 'La mer est plus belle' from Claude Debussy's Trois mélodies de Paul Verlaine, L. 81; Gabriel Fauré's Prison, Op. 83, No. 1; and 'Die Geister am Mummelsee' from Hugo Wolf's Mörike-Lieder, during the semi-finals of the International Vocal Competition 2021 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Het Noordbrabants Museum in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310081400 +0100" stop="20260310090900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Memory of a Concert</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Berliner Philharmonie. In 2006, Gidon Kremer and Martha Argerich set out on tour performing solos and duets by Bartók und Schumann. The last of the concert series at the Berliner Philharmonie has been recorded for this film, featuring a rare solo performance by Martha Argerich. A concert film with personal and moving commentary by Gidon Kremer. Program: Schumann's Violin Sonata No. 1, Op. 10, Violin Sonata No. 2, Op. 121; Kinderszenen, Op. 15; Bartók: Violin Sonata No. 1 Sz 75; Violin sonata No. 2 Sz 76.</desc>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310090900 +0100" stop="20260310093700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">PIAM - Semi-final I: Liszt and Ravel</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Auditorium Giorgio Gaber, Milan, Italy. Acclaimed classical music talent scout Antonio Mormone (1930-2017) lives on as the name-giver of the Premio Internazionale Antonio Mormone (PIAM), awarded to the winner of the Italian music competition of the same name. The first edition of this competition, which was held in various venues in Milan from 2019 to 2021, was dedicated to the piano. As part of this competition, Josef Edoardo Mossali (Italy, 2001) performs Franz Liszt's Apres une Lecture de Dante: Fantasia quasi Sonata; Maurice Ravel's Toccata from Le tombeau de Couperin; and Etude No. 3 "La Campanella" from Liszt's Six Grandes études de Paganini. This performance was recorded at Teatro EDI Barrio's in Milan, in February 2020.</desc>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310093700 +0100" stop="20260310100500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Classica Spotlight</title>
    <date>2010</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310100500 +0100" stop="20260310111000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Last Sonatas, Op. 109, 110 &amp; 111</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Château de Crevercoer-en-Brie and Château du Bois du Rocher, France. Beethoven's last three sonatas - Opus 109, 110 and 111 - explore the intimate meanders of the human soul, from despair to transfiguration. At the time of their composition, Beethoven was already locked in himself by his deafness. This deeply affected his relationship to others and to the world. This "psychological framework" is explored by director Mariano Nante, setting pianist Alexandre Tharaud in a film inspired by the universe of Tarkovski. Filmed in abandoned castles, and lit by director of photography Yorgos Arvanitis, this work evokes solitude and introspection and offers an inner journey through images and music.</desc>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310111000 +0100" stop="20260310124000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Piano works by Rachmaninoff, Beethoven &amp; Glazunov</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Tchaikovsky Concert Hall, Moscow, Russia. Russian pianist Nikolay Lugansky has received world-wide praise for his interpretations of the music of Sergei Rachmaninoff. In this wonderful recital, the great pianist presents works by the Russian Romantic composer as well as Ludwig van Beethoven and Alexander Glazunov. Lugansky opens his concert with Beethoven's Piano Sonata No. 14 in C-sharp minor, Op. 27 No. 2, 'Moonlight', followed by Alexander Glazunov's Piano Sonata No. 2 in E minor, Op. 75. Then Lugansky performs a selection of works by Rachmaninoff: Rachmaninoff's piano transcription of J. S. Bach's Partita No. 3 in E major; a selection of Études-Tableaux (Nos. 1, 2, 4, and 8, Op, 33, and Nos. 5 and 6, Op. 39); Lilac (Op. 21, No. 5); Prelude in C minor, Op. 23 No. 7; and Rachmaninoff's transcription of Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky's Lullaby (Op. 16 No. 1). This performance was recorded at the Tchaikovsky Concert Hall in Moscow, Russia, on June 4, 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310124000 +0100" stop="20260310132300 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">My heart is burning</title>
    <date>2006</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310132300 +0100" stop="20260310134600 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Mozart - Violin Concerto No. 4</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Cité de la Musique, Paris. Les Dissonances is a collective of artists founded by violinist David Grimal in 2004. The conductorless ensemble consists of musicians from the most prestigious European orchestras, international soloists, and young talents. In this performance, Les Dissonances play Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart's Violin Concerto No. 4 in D major, K. 218. Leading violinist Grimal features as the soloist. With the exception of the first violin concerto, Mozart composed his other four violin concertos in 1775 at a time when he was concertmaster at the Salzburg court. Among his five concertos, Violin Concerto No. 4 is one of the best-known. This performance was recorded at Cité de la Musique, France, in 2014.</desc>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310134600 +0100" stop="20260310140700 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - Brandenburg Concerto No. 5</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Hall of Mirrors, Castle of Köthen, Germany. J. S. Bach's six Brandenburg Concerto's belong to his best-known works. The composer wrote these concertos between 1711 and 1720 and dedicated them in 1721 to Christian Ludwig, Margrave of Brandenburg. In celebration of the pieces' 300th anniversary, Czech harpsichordist and conductor Václav Luks and the renowned Baroque ensemble Collegium 1704 recorded all six Brandenburg Concertos on historical instruments in 2021. The concertos are based on the Italian concerto grosso form, in which a group of solo instruments is set against a large ensemble. Bach's Brandenburg Concertos feature remarkable combinations of solo instruments and virtuoso solos. In this performance at the Hall of Mirrors in the Köthen Castle, Germany, Luks and his Collegium 1704 present Bach's Brandenburg Concerto No. 5 in D major, BWV 1050. Remarkably, the harpsichord appears as a solo instrument here, along with the flute and violin, rather than as an accompanying instrument. The piece is therefore considered one of Bach's very first keyboard concertos.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310140700 +0100" stop="20260310151400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Josquin - Missa L'homme armé sexti toni</title>
    <date>2018</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310151400 +0100" stop="20260310162500 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Tchaikovsky Symphony 2 &amp; Elgar's Enigma Variations</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino, Florence, Italy. The Maggio Musicale Fiorentino (Florence Musical May) is Italy's oldest opera and arts festival. It was founded in 1933 with the aim of presenting contemporary and forgotten operas. Over the years, the scope widened, and orchestral concerts have long been an integral part of the festival. As part of the festival's 2021 edition, Sir John Eliot Gardiner leads the Orchestra del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in a wonderful concert program that includes Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky's Symphony No. 2 in C minor, Op. 17, 'Little Russian', and Edward Elgar's Variations on an Original Theme, Op. 36, better known as the Enigma Variations. Written in 1872, Tchaikovsky's Symphony No. 2 bears the nickname 'Little Russian', as the composer used folk tunes in his work from Ukraine, then known as 'Little Russia'. Completed in 1899, Elgar's Enigma Variations is an orchestral work comprising a theme and fourteen variations, each variation being a musical sketch of one of the composer's friends. This performance was recorded at Teatro del Maggio Musicale Fiorentino in Florence, Italy, in 2021.</desc>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310162500 +0100" stop="20260310173900 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 9 in D minor, Op. 125</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Opéra Bastille, Paris, France. Swiss conductor Philippe Jordan and the Orchestre de l'Opéra national de Paris recorded all of Ludwig van Beethoven's symphonies in 2014-2015. In this program, maestro Jordan presents Beethoven's final symphony: Symphony No. 9 in D minor, Op. 125. He conducts the Orchestre and Choeurs de l'Opéra national de Paris and four vocal soloists Ricarda Merbeth (soprano), Daniela Sindram (mezzosoprano), Robert Dean Smith (tenor), and Günther Groissböck (bass). Beethoven composed his last Symphony when his hearing had all but gone, between 1822 and 1824. Symphony No. 9 is the longest and most ambitious of Beethoven's symphonies. Most striking is the piece's finale movement, which includes a choir and four vocal soloists singing a setting of Friedrich Schiller's poem 'An die Freude' (Ode to Joy). This performance was recorded at Opéra Bastille in Paris, France, in 2015.</desc>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310173900 +0100" stop="20260310192200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Europakonzert 2007 - Berlin</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Kabelwerk Oberspree, Berlin. The 2007 Europa-Konzert takes place in Berlin, on the occasion of the 125th anniversary of the Berliner Philharmoniker. Under the theme "The Year 1882", the acclaimed orchestra is lead by conductor Sir Simon Rattle as it interprets Brahms' "Concerto for violin, cello and orchestra", his Fourth Symphony and Wagners' "Prelude to Act I" from Parsifal - the piece that marked the orchestra's first recorded work of September 1913 under the baton of Alfred Hertz. The soloists are Lisa Batiashvili (violin) and Truls Mork (cello), established as sought-after young virtuosos and appearing regularly with leading orchestras and in recitals throughout the world. The "Kraftwerk und Kabelwerk Oberspree (power and cable factory)", the remarkable venue of this concert, is one of the most impressive historical industrial building from the late 19th century in Berlin. As its impressive presence is infused with Brahms and Wagner, there is an air of total commitment, only enhanced further by the unusual surroundings. The collaboration of Lisa Batiashvili and Truls Mork ensures a moving performance of Brahms's last orchestral work, his Double Concerto. Following this, Rattle and the orchestra continue to demonstrate their outstanding musicianship, delivering Wagner's amazingly fresh and dynamic Fourth Symphony.</desc>
    <date>2007</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310192200 +0100" stop="20260310194400 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Bach - Cello Suite No. 5 in C minor, BWV 1011</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310194400 +0100" stop="20260310200000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Summertime at the Domaine Forget</title>
    <date>2016</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310200000 +0100" stop="20260310210100 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 3 in E-flat major, Op. 55</title>
    <date>2020</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310210100 +0100" stop="20260310214800 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven - Symphony No. 6</title>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310214800 +0100" stop="20260310222200 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">IVC 2019 - Final: Haydn, Schubert et al</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Theater aan de Parade, 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands. Mezzo-soprano Ema Nikolovska (Canada, 1993) and pianist Michael Sikich (United States, 1993) perform 'The sailor's song' from Joseph Haydn's Six original canzonettas, Book 2 - Hob. XXVIa; Franz Schubert's Auf dem See, Op. 92 No. 2 (D. 543); 'Botschaft' from Johannes Brahms's Fünf Lieder, Op. 47; 'Röselein, Röselein!' from Robert Schumann's Sechs Gesänge, Op. 89; 'A girl' and 'Pan is dead' from Robert Heppener's Four songs on poems by Ezra Pound; 'La Flute de Pan' and 'La chevelure' from Claude Debussy's Trois chansons de Bilitis, L. 90; Pauline Viardot's 'Hai luli!'; and 'Produzhdeniye vesni' (Spring awakening), and 'Kreytserova sonata' (Kreutzer sonata) from Dmitri Shostakovich's Satiri (Satires - Pictures of the past), Op. 109, during the final round of the International Vocal Competition 2019 - Lied Duo. This performance was recorded at Theater aan de Parade in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands.</desc>
    <date>2019</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310222200 +0100" stop="20260311000000 +0100" channel="Stingray Classica">
    <title lang="pl">Chopin - Piano Concertos No. 1 &amp; No. 2</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Warsaw Philharmonic Concert Hall. Antoni Wit conducts the Warsaw Philharmonic Orchestra in performances of Chopin's Piano Concertos No. 1, Op. 11 and No. 2, Op. 21. Soloists are Nikolai Demidenko and Evgeny Kissin. After performing the first concerto, Demidenko encores with Chopin's Mazurka Op. 17/4. Kissin closes the concert with Chopin's Etude Op. 10/12 and the Waltz in E minor, Op. post. This concert was part of the celebration of Chopin's 200th anniversary in 2010. Chopin composed the second concerto one year before the Concerto No. 1 and completed both works at the age of 20, before leaving his home country Poland and moving to Paris.</desc>
    <date>2010</date>
    <category lang="pl">concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
    <rating>
      <value>0</value>
    </rating>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305003300 +0100" stop="20260305014300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Manu Dibango - Multiplatino</title>
    <date>1983</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305014300 +0100" stop="20260305043700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Strauss: Arabella - Teatro Real de Madrid</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Arabella 'Lyrische Komödie' in three acts Richard Strauss (1864-1949) Libretto by Hugo von Hofmannsthal First performance at Dresden, Sächsisches Staatstheater, 1 July 1933 Principal Chorus and Orchestra of the Teatro Real, David Afkham (conductor) Andrés Máspero (Chorus Director) Christof Loy (Stage Direction) Herbert Murauer (Stage and Costume Design), Reinhard Traub (Lighting), Thomas Wilhelm (Choreography) Jacquelyn Wagner (Arabella) Sarah Defrise (Zdenka) Martin Winkler (Count Waldner) Anne Sofie von Otter (Adelaide) Josef Wagner (Mandryka) Matthew Newlin (Matteo) Dean Power (Count Elemer) Roger Smeets (Count Dominik) Tyler Zimmerman (Count Lamoral) Madrid, Teatro Real, 9 February 2023.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jérémie Cuvillier</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa5028629.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305043700 +0100" stop="20260305044900 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Steinway &amp; Sons</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Go behind the scenes at the Steinway &amp; Sons factory and discover Spirio, the incredible technology that allows a piano to replay a performance exactly as it was played live. Mr. Guido Zimmermann, the president of the world-famous pianomakers, talks us through the revolutionary concept, accompanied by images of the precise, fascinating craftmanship and engineering that goes into each one of the Spirio pianos. Hugo Cohen Sprung's documentary also allows us insight into French pianist and Steinway artist Bertrand Chamayou's experience with the technology and features a preview of his unique two-piano concert in which he performs with his 'shadow'.</desc>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419736.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305044900 +0100" stop="20260305064200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Orchestre de Paris, Khatia Buniatishvili, Klaus Mäkelä: Falla, Tchaikovsky, Debussy, Ravel</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Isabelle Soulard</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305064200 +0100" stop="20260305072800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jean-Yves Thibaudet, San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, Esa-Pekka Salonen: Scriabin - Prometheus</title>
    <desc lang="pl">San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, Esa-Pekka Salonen (conductor) Jean-Yves Thibaudet (piano) Mathilde Laurent (perfumer) Alexander Scriabin 1872 - 1915 Prometheus, The Poem of Fire Alexander Scriabin's symphonic poem 'Prometheus, The Poem of Fire' celebrates synesthesia and cosmic unity. Devised by San Francisco Symphony Music Director Esa-Pekka Salonen, pianist Jean-Yves Thibaudet, and Cartier in-house perfumer Mathilde Laurent, the San Francisco Symphony and Cartier present a multisensory production of 'Prometheus'. This collaborative world premiere combines dynamic musical and light performance with olfactory curation, subsuming audiences in Scriabin's creative vision more than a century after the piece of total art was composed. Directed by Sébastien Glas San Francisco, Davies Symphony Hall, 3 mars 2024.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sébastien Glas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305072800 +0100" stop="20260305092800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Paris Opera Competition 2022</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Orchestre Prométhée, Pierre-Michel Durand (Conductor) Florence Alayrac (Stage Direction) María Brea (soprano) Venezuela William Desbiens (baritone) Canada Anna Harvey (mezzo-soprano) UK George Vîrban (tenor) Romania María Carla Pino Cury (soprano) Chile Serena Sáenz Molinero (soprano) Spain Luke Scott (baritone) Scotland Aytaj Shikhalizada (mezzo-soprano) Azerbaijan Deniz Uzun (mezzo-soprano) Germany Paris Opera Competition Final Leo Delibes Lakmé 'Ou va la jeune Hindoue' Serena Sáenz Molinero Piotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky The Maid of Orleans 'Da tchas nastal' Deniz uzun Charles Gounod Faust 'Avant de quitter ces lieux' Luke scott Giuseppe Verdi La Traviata 'Parigi o cara' George Vîrban and María Brea Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart La Clemenza di Tito 'Parto, parto ma tu ben mio' Anna harvey Ambroise Thomas Hamlet 'Doute de la lumiere' William Desbiens and María Carla Pino Cury Gioachino Rossini L'Italiana in Algeri 'Cruda sorte' Aytaj Shikhalizada Il barbiere di Siviglia 'Ah qual colpo inaspettato' Deniz Uzun, George Vîrban and Luke Scott Gaetano Donizetti Linda di Chamounix 'O luce di quest'anima' María Carla Pino Cury Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov The Tsar's Bride 'Zachem ty' Aytaj Shikhalizada and William Desbiens Gustave Charpentier Louise 'Depuis le jour' María Brea Engelbert Humperdinck Hansel and Gretel 'Wie duftet's von dorten' Anna Harvey and María Carla Pino Cury Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart Cosi fan tutte 'Il core vi dono' Deniz Uzun and Luke Scott Piotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky Eugene Onegin 'Kuda, kuda' George Vîrban Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart Lucio Silla 'D'elisio in sen m'attendi' Aytaj Shakhalizada and Serena Sáenz Molinero Gioachino Rossini The Barber of Seville 'Largo al factotum della citta' William desbiens Richard strauss Der Rosenkavalier 'Marie Theres'! Hab 'mir's gelobt' María Brea, Anna Harvey and Serena Sáenz Molinero Gioachino Rossini L'Italiana in Algeri 'Va sossopra il mio cervello' Tutti Paris, Palais Garnier, January 22, 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sébastien Glas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305092800 +0100" stop="20260305100000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984464.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305100000 +0100" stop="20260305115400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">André Midani: An Insider's Story of Brazilian Music</title>
    <desc lang="pl">André Midani: An Insider's Story of Brazilian Music Based on his autobiography, this unique session of intimate conversations reveals the key events in the history of Brazilian music through the eyes of André Midani, who helped shape the Brazilian music scene like no other from the 1950s to the new millennium. With Gilberto Gil, Caetano Veloso, Marisa Monte, Chico Buarque, Frejat, Jorge Ben Jor, Erasmo Carlos, Boni, Fernanda Torres, Washington Olivetto, Carlos Lyra, Miúcha, Roberto Menescal, Baby Brazil, Dadi, Liminha, Nelson Motta, Carlos Diegues, Fernanda Montenegro - and many others Directed by Andrucha Waddington, Mini Kerti 2015.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Andrucha Waddington</director>
      <director>Mini Kerti</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2015</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419736.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305115400 +0100" stop="20260305125300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Aida Garifullina, Maciej Pikulski: Romantic arias and songs</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Aida Garifullina (Soprano), Maciej Pikulski (Piano) Gerónimo Giménez/Manuel Nieto El Barbero de Sevilla, II : 'Me llaman la primorosa' Carlos Gardel Por una cabeza Frédéric Chopin Trois valses, op. 64: no. 2 in C sharp minor Jules Massenet Élégie Georges Bizet Carmen : 'L'amour est un oiseau rebelle' Léo Delibes Les Filles de Cadix Franz Schubert/Franz Liszt Ständchen, S. 560/7 Antonín Dvorák Gypsy Songs, Op. 55 : IV. Kdyz mne stará matka zpívat ucívala (Songs My Mother Taught Me) Rusalka: 'Msicku na nebi hlubokém' (Song to the Moon) Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov The Golden Cockerel: The Queen of Shemakha's aria (Hymn to the Sun) Sergei Rachmaninov Zdes' khorosho, Op. 21, No. 7 Prelude, Op. 3, No. 2 Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov Sadko, Scene IV: Song of India Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky Iolanta: Iolanta's Arioso, 'Atchevo eta prezhde ne znala?' Six Romances, Op. 63 : 6. Serenada Giuseppe Verdi/Franz Liszt Rigoletto, Concert Paraphrase for Piano, S. 434 Franz Schubert Ave Maria, D. 839 Giacomo Puccini Tosca, II: Vissi d'arte Gianni Schicchi : 'O mio babbino caro' Ruggero Leoncavallo Mattinata Évian, La Grange au Lac, 3 July 2023 Directed by Jean-Pierre Loisil.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jean-Pierre Loisil</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305125300 +0100" stop="20260305131500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419708.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305131500 +0100" stop="20260305144500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Prix de Lausanne: Rising Stars Gala 2026</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Lausanne, Théâtre de Beaulieu, 8 February 2026.</desc>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="pl">balet</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419696.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305144500 +0100" stop="20260305163600 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Claudio Abbado, Berliner Philharmoniker: Beethoven, Brahms, Dvorák</title>
    <date>2002</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305163600 +0100" stop="20260305174000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Claudio Abbado 10 years after</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Claudio Abbado 10 years after.</desc>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419736.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305174000 +0100" stop="20260305203000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Serse' by Haendel at the Rouen Opera</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Serse Opera in three acts by Georg Friedrich Handel (1685 - 1759) Libretto by Nicolo Minato and Silvio Stampiglia First performnce in London, King's Theatre, 15 April 1738 Opéra de Rouen Normandie Orchestra, David Bates (Musical direction, harpsichord) Clarac &amp; Deloeuil &gt; The Lab (Stage Direction, sets, costumes) Christophe Pitoiset (Set design collaboration), Lodie Kardouss (Artistic collaboration), Rick Martin (Lights), Julien Roques and Benjamin Juhel (Video), Julien Roques (Graphic design), Luc Bourrousse (Dramaturgy) Jake Arditti (Serse) Jakub Józef Orlinski (Arsamene) Cecilia Molinari (Amastre) Mari Eriksmoen (Romilda) Sophie Junker (Atalanta) Luigi de Donato (Ariodate) Elviro Riccardo (Novaro) Rouen, Théâtre des Arts, March 14, 2023.</desc>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305203000 +0100" stop="20260305211300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Dizzy Gillespie Quartet - Berliner Jazztage</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sigrid Schröder</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1976</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305211300 +0100" stop="20260305215700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Gil Evans Orchestra &amp; Mccoy Tyner Sextet - Berliner Jazztage</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Oskar Krüger</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1976</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305215700 +0100" stop="20260305223800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Oregon - Berliner Jazztage</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Dieter Krause</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1980</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305223800 +0100" stop="20260305232100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jimmy Witherspoon Quartet - Multiplatino</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sandro Pedrazzetti</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1985</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305232100 +0100" stop="20260306002500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Beethoven: Symphony No. 5 - Insula Orchestra, Laurence Equilbey</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Anais Spiro</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306002500 +0100" stop="20260306021700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jonas Kaufmann, Ludovic Tézier - Verdi, Ponchielli - Baden-Baden</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Jonas Kaufmann (tenor), Ludovic Tézier (baritone) Deutsche Radio Philharmonie Saarbrücken Kaiserslautern, Jochen Rieder (Conductor) Giuseppe Verdi 1813 - 1901 La forza del destino : Oberture - Solenne in quest'ora - Morir! Tremenda cosa - La vita e inferno all'infelice Invano Alvaro ti celasti al mondo I vespri siciliani : Oberture Amilcare Ponchielli 1834 - 1886 La Gioconda : Enzo Grimaldi, Principe di Santafior - Danza delle ore - Cielo e mar Giuseppe Verdi Otello : Credo in un Dio crudel - Tu? Indietro! Directed by Andreas Morell Baden-Baden, Festspielhaus, 8 January 2023.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Andreas Morell</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306021700 +0100" stop="20260306041700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Elisabeth Leonskaja, Quatuor Danel: Shostakovich, Weinberg - Théâtre du Capitole, Toulouse</title>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306041700 +0100" stop="20260306053000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jerusalem Chamber Music Festival 2022: Weinberg, Bruch, Schubert</title>
    <credits>
      <director>John Blanch</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306053000 +0100" stop="20260306062200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Carl Nielsen - Between heaven and earth</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Magdalena Zięba-Schwind</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984494.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306062200 +0100" stop="20260306074300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Cappella Mediterranea: Amore siciliano - Leonardo García Alarcón</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Cappella Mediterranea, Leonardo García Alarcón (musical direction) Ana Vieira Leite (soprano), Mariana Flores (soprano), Léo Fernique (countertenor), Valerio Contaldo (tenor), Matteo Bellotto (bass) Vincenzo Tozzi (1612 - 1679) Qual Suono Roland de Lassus (1532 -1594) Kyrie eleison Anonimo Fermarono i cieli Tommaso Carapella (1665 -1736) Ho vinto, Amor Anonimo U Ciucciu Cataldo Amodei (1650 -1695) Va, ché l'hai fatto a me Anonimo La canzone di Cecilia Sigismondo d'India (1582 -1629) Mercé ! Grido piangendo Pasquale Carroza Amantissime Jesu (Sinfonia) Cataldo Amodei In solitare arene Corrado Bonfiglio Caro amante José Marín (1618- 1699) Ojos, pues me desdenáis Giovanni M. Trabaci (1575 - 1647) Canzona francesa cromatica Sigismondo d'India Dispietata Pietate Cataldo Amodei La Parca Tirannide Vezzosa Anonimo A riturnella Santiago de Murcia (1673-1739) Tarantela Espanola Alessandro Scarlatti (1660 -1725) Mori mi dici Sigismondo d'India Piangono al pianger moi Leonardo García Alarcón (1976 - ) Madrigal in 5 in fugue on La Canzone di Cecilia Chantilly, Les Coups de Ceur de Chantilly, 12 October 2025.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Julien Condemine</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306074300 +0100" stop="20260306081500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Keller Quartet - Brahms: String Quartet No.1</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Janos Darvas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1994</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306081500 +0100" stop="20260306084600 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Keller Quartet - Brahms: String Quartet No.2</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Janos Darvas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1994</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306084600 +0100" stop="20260306100000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Keller Quartet - Brahms: String Quartet No.3</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Janos Darvas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1994</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306100000 +0100" stop="20260306111700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Christian Spuck: Poppea // Poppea - Gauthier Dance</title>
    <desc lang="pl">POPPEA // POPPEA by Christian Spuck Choregraphed by Christian Spuck for Gauthier Dance Music by Martin Donner, Claudio Monteverdi and others Gauthier Dance Emma Ryott - Set designer, costume designer Dunja Funke - Dramaturgy Reinhard Traub - Lighting Eric Gauthier - Dancer Anneleen Dedroog - Dancer Miriam Gronwald - Dancer Anna Süheyla Harms - Dancer Maria Prat Balasch - Dancer Rosario Guerra - Dancer Florian Lochner - Dancer William Moragas - Dancer David Stiven Valencia Martinez - Dancer Tars Vandebeek - Dancer Directed by Nikolai Vialkowitsch Stuttgart, Theaterhaus Stuttgart, 2013.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Nikolai Vialkowitsch</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">balet</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419696.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306111700 +0100" stop="20260306125100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Les Siecles, Adrien Perruchon: Ravel</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Stéphane Vérité</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306125100 +0100" stop="20260306133000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984460.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306133000 +0100" stop="20260306162200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Puccini: Il Trittico - Théâtre de la Monnaie</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Il Trittico Three operas in one act by Giacomo Puccini 1858 -1924 Il Tabarro Libretto by Giuseppe Adami, based on 'La Houppelande' by Didier Gold Suor Angelica Libretto by Giovacchino Forzano Gianni Schicchi Libretto by Giovacchino Forzano, based on an episode in Dante's 'Divine Comedy' First performance in New York, Metropolitan Opera, December 14, 1918 La Monnaie Symphony Orchestra and Choirs, La Monnaie Children's and Youth Choirs, Alain Altinoglu (Musical Direction) Alberto Moro (Choir leader) Tobias Kratzer (Director) Rainer Sellmaier (Sets &amp; costumes), Bernd Purkrabek (Lighting), Manuel Braun (Video) Il Tabarro Peter Kálmán (Michele) Corinne Winters (Giorgetta) Adam Smith (Luigi Amante) Roberto Covatta (Il Tinca) Giovanni Furlanetto (Il Talpa) Maxime Melnik (Un venditore di canzonette) Annunziata Vestri (La Frugola) Benedetta Torre (Amante) Suor Angelica Corinne Winters (Suor Angelica) Raehann Bryce-Davis (La zia principessa) Elena Zilio (La badessa) Annunziata Vestri (La suora zelatrice) Tineke Van Ingelgem (La maestra delle novizie La suora infirmiera) Benedetta Torre (Suor Genovieffa) Annelies Kerstens (Suor Osmina) Raphaële Green (Suor Dolcina) Karen Vermeiren (Prima sorella cercatrice) Marta Beretta (Seconda sorella cercatrice) Emma Posman (Una novizia) Gianni Schicchi Peter Kálmán (Gianni Schicchi) Benedetta Torre (Lauretta) Elena Zilio (Zita) Adam Smith (Rinuccio) Roberto Covatta (Gherardo) Karen Vermeiren (Nella) Luca Dall'Amico (Betto di Signa) Giovanni Furlanetto (Simone) Gabriele Nani (Marco) Tineke Van Ingelgem (La Ciesca) Roberto Accurso (Maestro Spinelloccio Ser Amantio di Nicolao) Kurt Gysen (Pinellino) Lucas Cortoos (Guccio) Henri de Beauffort (Gherardino) Gerard Lavalle (Buoso Donati) Brussels, Théâtre de la Monnaie / De Munt, April 30, 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jérémie Cuvillier</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306162200 +0100" stop="20260306172000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984464.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306172000 +0100" stop="20260306180800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Mel Lewis Orchestra - Multiplatino</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sandro Pedrazzetti</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1985</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306180800 +0100" stop="20260306185900 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">McCoy Tyner: Piano Solo</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Janos Darvas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1983</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306185900 +0100" stop="20260306203000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Robin McKelle: A Tribute to Ella Fitzgerald</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sebastien Berge</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306203000 +0100" stop="20260306221100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Orchestre de Paris, Esa-Pekka Salonen, Aliisa Neige Barriere: Saariaho, Sibelius, Lindberg</title>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306221100 +0100" stop="20260306233100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Claudio Abbado, Berliner Philharmoniker: Brahms</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Bob Coles</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1997</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306233100 +0100" stop="20260307020800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Massenet: Thais - Opéra de Monte-Carlo</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Thais 'Comédie lyrique' in three acts by Jules Massenet (1842 - 1912) Libretto by Louis Gallet based on the novel by Anatole France First performance in Paris, Opéra, 16 March 1894 Monte-Carlo Philharmonic Orchestra, Jean-Yves Ossonce (conductor) Monte-Carlo Opera Chorus Jean-Louis Grinda (Stage director) Marina Rebeka (Thais) Ludovic Tézier (Athanaël) Jean-François Borras (Nicias) Philippe Kahn (Palémon) Marie Gautrot (Albine) Cassandre Berthon (Crobyle) Valentine Lemercier (Myrtale) Jennifer Courcier (La Charmeuse) Directed by Gabriel Grinda Monte-Carlo, Opera, 28 January 2021.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gabriel Grinda</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa5028629.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307020800 +0100" stop="20260307030100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Wagner´s Jews</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Wagner´s Jews Richard Wagner was notoriously anti-Semitic, and his writings on Jews were later embraced by Hitler and the Nazis. But for years, many of Wagner's closest associates were Jews - young musicians who became personally devoted to him, and provided crucial help to his work and career. Why were they drawn to him? And how could Wagner even accept their embrace? These questions are at the heart of 'Wagner's Jews', the first film to focus on Wagner's complex personal relationships with Jews. Filmed on location in Germany, Switzerland, and Italy, 'Wagner's Jews' reveals this remarkable story through archival sources, re-enactments, interviews, and performances of original musical works by Wagner's Jewish colleagues. Featuring Zubin Mehta and Leon Botstein among others, the film also explores the ongoing controversy over performing Wagner's music in Israel. The same questions asked in Wagner's time still resonate today: is it possible to separate the art from its creator? Can sublime music transcend prejudice and bigotry, and the weight of history? Directed by Hilan Warshaw 2013.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Hilan Warshaw</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984494.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307030100 +0100" stop="20260307031300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Steinway &amp; Sons</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Go behind the scenes at the Steinway &amp; Sons factory and discover Spirio, the incredible technology that allows a piano to replay a performance exactly as it was played live. Mr. Guido Zimmermann, the president of the world-famous pianomakers, talks us through the revolutionary concept, accompanied by images of the precise, fascinating craftmanship and engineering that goes into each one of the Spirio pianos. Hugo Cohen Sprung's documentary also allows us insight into French pianist and Steinway artist Bertrand Chamayou's experience with the technology and features a preview of his unique two-piano concert in which he performs with his 'shadow'.</desc>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984494.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307031300 +0100" stop="20260307050700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Orchestre de Paris, Khatia Buniatishvili, Klaus Mäkelä: Falla, Tchaikovsky, Debussy, Ravel</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Isabelle Soulard</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307050700 +0100" stop="20260307063700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Benjamin Bernheim, Berliner Philharmoniker, Kirill Petrenko: New Year's Eve Concert 2025</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Berliner Philharmoniker, Kirill Petrenko (conductor) Benjamin Bernheim (ténor) Piotr Tchaikovsky 1840 - 1893 Eugen Onegin, op. 24 Polonaise - Introduction, Scene and Lensky's Aria from Act 2 Gabriel Fauré 1845 - 1924 Pelléas et Mélisande, orchestral suite, op. 80 Sicilienne Charles Gounod 1818 - 1893 Roméo et Juliette L'amour ! (Act 2) Piotr Tchaikovsky Romeo and Juliet, Fantasy Overture after Shakespeare Jules Massenet 1842 - 1912 Werther Prelude to Act 1 - Pourquoi me réveiller (Act 3) Georges Bizet 1838 - 1875 L'Arlésienne, Suite No. 2 Farandole Carmen La fleur que tu m'avais jetée (Act 2) Emmanuel Chabrier 1841 - 1894 Espana, Rhapsody for orchestra George Gershwin 1898 - 1937 Cuban Overture Berlin, Philharmonie, 31 December 2025.</desc>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307063700 +0100" stop="20260307080000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">La Neuvieme Symphonie By Maurice Béjart - Béjart Ballet Lausanne, Tokyo Ballet</title>
    <desc lang="pl">The Ninth Symhony Maurice Béjart, choreography After Schiller's 'Ode to joy' Ludwig van Beethoven, music Maurice Béjart, staging Friedrich Nietzsche, Prologue Gil Roman, artistic director Israel Philharmonic orchestra Zubin Mehta, conductor Ritsuyukai choir Kufiami Kuriyama, chorus master Gil Roman, narratorr Kristin Lewis, soprano Mihoko Fujimura, mezzo-soprano Kei Fukui, tenor Alexander Vinogradov, bass JB Meier and Thierry Hochstätter, percussion Joëlle Roustan abd Roger Bernard, original costumes and sets Henri Davila, costumes adaptation Dominique Roman, Lighting realisation Piotr Nardelli, Ballet Master revival With The Béjart Ballet Lausanne The Tokyo Ballet and Solooists Dan Tsukamoto, Mizuka Ueno, Iori Nittono, Aya Takagi, Kathleen Thielheilm, Masayoshi Onuki, Elisabet Ros, Juien Favreau, Lisa Cano, Fabrice Gallarrague, Pauline Voisard, Felipe Rocha, Oscar Chacon, Keisuke Nasuno, Marsha Rodriguez, Cosima Munoz, Mari Ohashi, Kwinten Guilliams, Aldriana Vargas Lopez, Hector Navarro, Alanna Archibald Recorded on November 9 th 2014 at the NHK Hall Tokyo TV Director, Mari Hnamasu.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Mari Hnamasu</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">balet</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa5028531.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307080000 +0100" stop="20260307091100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jerusalem Chamber Music Festival: Rachmaninov, Weinberg</title>
    <credits>
      <director>John Blanch</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307091100 +0100" stop="20260307100000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984460.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307100000 +0100" stop="20260307123900 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Magnard: Guerceur - Opéra du Rhin</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Guerceur Opera in three acts by Albéric Magnard 1865 - 1914 Libretto by the composer First performed in Paris, Opéra, 23 April 1931 Orchestre philharmonique de Strasbourg, Cheur de l'Opéra national du Rhin, Ingo Metzmacher (Conductor) Hendrik Haas (chorus master) Christof Loy (Director) Johannes Leiacker (Set Design), Ursula Renzenbrink (Costumes), Olaf Winter (Lighting) Stéphane Degout (Guerceur) Catherine Hunold (Vérité) Antoinette Dennefeld (Giselle) Julien Henric (Heurtal) Eugénie Joneau (Bonté) Gabrielle Philiponet (Beauté) Adriana Bignagni Lesca (Souffrance) Marie Lenormand (L'Ombre d'une femme) Alysia Hanshaw (L'Ombre d'une vierge) Glen Cunningham (L'Ombre d'un poete) Strasbourg, Opéra du Rhin, 4 May 2024.</desc>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307123900 +0100" stop="20260307133000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984464.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307133000 +0100" stop="20260307144000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Manu Dibango - Multiplatino</title>
    <date>1983</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307144000 +0100" stop="20260307155100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Joachim Kühn in Concert - Klaviersommer</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Dieter Hens</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1999</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307155100 +0100" stop="20260307163400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jimmy Witherspoon Quartet - Multiplatino</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sandro Pedrazzetti</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1985</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307163400 +0100" stop="20260307174000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jean-Yves Thibaudet, San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, Esa-Pekka Salonen: Scriabin - Prometheus</title>
    <desc lang="pl">San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, Esa-Pekka Salonen (conductor) Jean-Yves Thibaudet (piano) Mathilde Laurent (perfumer) Alexander Scriabin 1872 - 1915 Prometheus, The Poem of Fire Alexander Scriabin's symphonic poem 'Prometheus, The Poem of Fire' celebrates synesthesia and cosmic unity. Devised by San Francisco Symphony Music Director Esa-Pekka Salonen, pianist Jean-Yves Thibaudet, and Cartier in-house perfumer Mathilde Laurent, the San Francisco Symphony and Cartier present a multisensory production of 'Prometheus'. This collaborative world premiere combines dynamic musical and light performance with olfactory curation, subsuming audiences in Scriabin's creative vision more than a century after the piece of total art was composed. Directed by Sébastien Glas San Francisco, Davies Symphony Hall, 3 mars 2024.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sébastien Glas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307174000 +0100" stop="20260307190900 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">International Conducting Competition Rotterdam 2025</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Nander Cirkel</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307190900 +0100" stop="20260307203000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Sonya Yoncheva, Malcolm Martineau - Rencontres Musicales d'Evian</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Mariano Nante</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307203000 +0100" stop="20260307224200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Verdi : Falstaff - Opéra de Lille</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Falstaff 'Commedia lirica' in three acts by Giuseppe Verdi (1813-1901) Libretto by Arrigo Boito First performance in Milan, Teatro alla Scala, February 9, 1893 Orchestre National de Lille, Cheur de l'Opéra de Lille Antonello Allemandi (conductor) Denis Podalydes (stage director) Éric Ruf (sets), Christian Lacroix (costumes), Bertrand Couderc (lights) Tassis Christoyannis (Falstaff) Gabrielle Philiponet (Alice Ford) Julie Robard-Gendre (Meg Page) Silvia Beltrami (Mrs Quickly) Clara Guillon (Nannetta) Gezim Myshketa (Ford) Kevin Amiel (Fenton) Luca Lombardo (Dr Caius) Loic Felix (Bardolfo) Damien Pass (Pistola) Laurent Podalydes, Léo Reynaud (actors) Lille, Opera, May 14, 2023.</desc>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307224200 +0100" stop="20260308003600 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Claudio Abbado, Berliner Philharmoniker: Beethoven, Brahms, Dvorák</title>
    <date>2002</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308003600 +0100" stop="20260308013100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Naissam Jalal: Landscapes of Eternity - Jazz sous les Pommiers</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Samuel Thiebaut</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308013100 +0100" stop="20260308030900 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Orchestre Symphonique de Montréal, Bruce Liu, Dalia Stasevska - Chopin, Gubaidulina, Sibelius</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Benoît Guérin</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308030900 +0100" stop="20260308045200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Young Euro Classic 2022: Chineke! Junior Orchestra, Glass Marcano</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Andreas Morell</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308045200 +0100" stop="20260308072200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Delibes : Lakmé - Jodie Devos</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Lakmé Opera in three acts by Léo Delibes (1836 - 1891) Libretto by Edmond Gondinet and Philippe Gille after Pierre Lotti First performance in Paris, Opéra Comique, April 14, 1883 Orchestra and Chorus of the Royal Opera of Wallonia-Liege, Frédéric Chaslin (Conductor) Davide Garattini Raimondi, Marie Neyrinck (Stage direction) Paolo Vitale (Sets, Lights), Arnaud Doffagne (Lights), Giada Masi (Costumes), Barbara Palumbo (Choreography) Jodie Devos (Lakmé) Philippe Talbot (Gérald) Lionel Lhote as Nilakantha Pierre Doyen (Frédéric) Marion Lebegue (Mallika) Julie Mossay (Miss Ellen) Sarah LaulanMiss Bentson Pierre Romainville (Hadji) Caroline De Mahieu (Rose) Liege, Opéra Royal, September 20, 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Stéphane Vérité</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308072200 +0100" stop="20260308073400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Steinway &amp; Sons</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Go behind the scenes at the Steinway &amp; Sons factory and discover Spirio, the incredible technology that allows a piano to replay a performance exactly as it was played live. Mr. Guido Zimmermann, the president of the world-famous pianomakers, talks us through the revolutionary concept, accompanied by images of the precise, fascinating craftmanship and engineering that goes into each one of the Spirio pianos. Hugo Cohen Sprung's documentary also allows us insight into French pianist and Steinway artist Bertrand Chamayou's experience with the technology and features a preview of his unique two-piano concert in which he performs with his 'shadow'.</desc>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984494.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308073400 +0100" stop="20260308092800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Orchestre de Paris, Khatia Buniatishvili, Klaus Mäkelä: Falla, Tchaikovsky, Debussy, Ravel</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Isabelle Soulard</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308092800 +0100" stop="20260308100000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Bomsori Kim, Camerata Salzburg - Mozart: Violin Concerto No.4</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Alexander Radulescu</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308100000 +0100" stop="20260308113200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Madeleine Peyroux at Bordeaux's Grand-Théâtre</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Born in the United States, Madeleine Peyroux is a jazz singer and guitarist with an unclassifiable style and an exceptional artistic personality, carried by a voice that is both soft and husky, with blues and folk accents. After spending part of her childhood in the United States, she moved to France as a teenager where she joined her first jazz bands. An atypical artist, she performs a lot in the street while participating in festivals and creating her own albums. In 2004, she had an international success with Careless Love. Other albums have been released since, including the recent Anthem (2018), the title of which is taken from a Leonard Cohen song.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sîla</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308113200 +0100" stop="20260308124800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Robin McKelle: A Tribute to Ella Fitzgerald</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sebastien Berge</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308124800 +0100" stop="20260308134700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Aida Garifullina, Maciej Pikulski: Romantic arias and songs</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Aida Garifullina (Soprano), Maciej Pikulski (Piano) Gerónimo Giménez/Manuel Nieto El Barbero de Sevilla, II : 'Me llaman la primorosa' Carlos Gardel Por una cabeza Frédéric Chopin Trois valses, op. 64: no. 2 in C sharp minor Jules Massenet Élégie Georges Bizet Carmen : 'L'amour est un oiseau rebelle' Léo Delibes Les Filles de Cadix Franz Schubert/Franz Liszt Ständchen, S. 560/7 Antonín Dvorák Gypsy Songs, Op. 55 : IV. Kdyz mne stará matka zpívat ucívala (Songs My Mother Taught Me) Rusalka: 'Msicku na nebi hlubokém' (Song to the Moon) Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov The Golden Cockerel: The Queen of Shemakha's aria (Hymn to the Sun) Sergei Rachmaninov Zdes' khorosho, Op. 21, No. 7 Prelude, Op. 3, No. 2 Nikolai Rimsky-Korsakov Sadko, Scene IV: Song of India Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky Iolanta: Iolanta's Arioso, 'Atchevo eta prezhde ne znala?' Six Romances, Op. 63 : 6. Serenada Giuseppe Verdi/Franz Liszt Rigoletto, Concert Paraphrase for Piano, S. 434 Franz Schubert Ave Maria, D. 839 Giacomo Puccini Tosca, II: Vissi d'arte Gianni Schicchi : 'O mio babbino caro' Ruggero Leoncavallo Mattinata Évian, La Grange au Lac, 3 July 2023 Directed by Jean-Pierre Loisil.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jean-Pierre Loisil</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308134700 +0100" stop="20260308144500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Bomsori Kim, Camerata Salzburg - Mozart: Violin Concerto No.5</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Alexander Radulescu</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308144500 +0100" stop="20260308171500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Puccini: Manon Lescaut - Opéra de Monte-Carlo</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Manon Lescaut 'Dramma lirico' in four acts by Giacomo Puccini (1858-1924) Libretto by Mario Praga, Domenico Oliva, Giulio Ricordi, Luigi Illica and Giuseppe Giacosa based on the abbé Prévost First performance in Torino, Teatro Regio, 1 February 1893 Orchestre Philharmonique de Monte-Carlo, Cheur de l'Opéra de Monte-Carlo, Pinchas Steinberg (Conductor) Stefano Visconti (Chorus Master) Guy Montavon (Stage Direction, lighting) Hank Irwin Kittel (sets), Christopher Kempf (Costumes) Anna Netrebko (Manon Lescaut) Claudio Sgura (Lescaut) Yusif Eyvazov (Des Grieux) Alessandro Spina (Geronte di Ravoir) Luis Gomes (Edmond) Rémy Mathieu (Dance Master) Luca Vianello (The Innkeeper) Loriana Castellano (a musician) Monte-Carlo, Opéra, 22 April 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Gabriel Grinda</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308171500 +0100" stop="20260308185600 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Orchestre de Paris, Esa-Pekka Salonen, Aliisa Neige Barriere: Saariaho, Sibelius, Lindberg</title>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308185600 +0100" stop="20260308203000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Youn Sun Nah Quartet - Annecy</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Samuel Thiebaut</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308203000 +0100" stop="20260308221200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Royal Concertgebouw, Mirga Grazinyte-Tyla, Gabriela Montero: Serksnyte, Tchaikovsky, Weinberg</title>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308221200 +0100" stop="20260308222300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Steinway &amp; Sons</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Go behind the scenes at the Steinway &amp; Sons factory and discover Spirio, the incredible technology that allows a piano to replay a performance exactly as it was played live. Mr. Guido Zimmermann, the president of the world-famous pianomakers, talks us through the revolutionary concept, accompanied by images of the precise, fascinating craftmanship and engineering that goes into each one of the Spirio pianos. Hugo Cohen Sprung's documentary also allows us insight into French pianist and Steinway artist Bertrand Chamayou's experience with the technology and features a preview of his unique two-piano concert in which he performs with his 'shadow'.</desc>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984494.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308222300 +0100" stop="20260308235700 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Martha Argerich, Maria Joao Pires, Orchestre de la Suisse Romande, Daniel Harding: Mozart, Mahler</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Andy Sommer</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308235700 +0100" stop="20260309023600 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Anna Karenina by John Neumeier - Hamburg Ballett</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Myriam Hoyer</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">balet</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419696.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309023600 +0100" stop="20260309051300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Serse' by Haendel at the Rouen Opera</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Serse Opera in three acts by Georg Friedrich Handel (1685 - 1759) Libretto by Nicolo Minato and Silvio Stampiglia First performnce in London, King's Theatre, 15 April 1738 Opéra de Rouen Normandie Orchestra, David Bates (Musical direction, harpsichord) Clarac &amp; Deloeuil &gt; The Lab (Stage Direction, sets, costumes) Christophe Pitoiset (Set design collaboration), Lodie Kardouss (Artistic collaboration), Rick Martin (Lights), Julien Roques and Benjamin Juhel (Video), Julien Roques (Graphic design), Luc Bourrousse (Dramaturgy) Jake Arditti (Serse) Jakub Józef Orlinski (Arsamene) Cecilia Molinari (Amastre) Mari Eriksmoen (Romilda) Sophie Junker (Atalanta) Luigi de Donato (Ariodate) Elviro Riccardo (Novaro) Rouen, Théâtre des Arts, March 14, 2023.</desc>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa5028629.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309051300 +0100" stop="20260309055600 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Dizzy Gillespie Quartet - Berliner Jazztage</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sigrid Schröder</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1976</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309055600 +0100" stop="20260309064000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Gil Evans Orchestra &amp; Mccoy Tyner Sextet - Berliner Jazztage</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Oskar Krüger</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1976</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309064000 +0100" stop="20260309072200 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Oregon - Berliner Jazztage</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Dieter Krause</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1980</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309072200 +0100" stop="20260309080500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jimmy Witherspoon Quartet - Multiplatino</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sandro Pedrazzetti</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1985</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309080500 +0100" stop="20260309092400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Claudio Abbado, Berliner Philharmoniker: Brahms</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Bob Coles</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1997</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309092400 +0100" stop="20260309094500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309094500 +0100" stop="20260309112400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Young Euro Classic 2025: European Union Youth Orchestra</title>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309112400 +0100" stop="20260309133000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">John Eliot Gardiner conducts Bach' Mass in B minor</title>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309133000 +0100" stop="20260309162300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Strauss: Arabella - Teatro Real de Madrid</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Arabella 'Lyrische Komödie' in three acts Richard Strauss (1864-1949) Libretto by Hugo von Hofmannsthal First performance at Dresden, Sächsisches Staatstheater, 1 July 1933 Principal Chorus and Orchestra of the Teatro Real, David Afkham (conductor) Andrés Máspero (Chorus Director) Christof Loy (Stage Direction) Herbert Murauer (Stage and Costume Design), Reinhard Traub (Lighting), Thomas Wilhelm (Choreography) Jacquelyn Wagner (Arabella) Sarah Defrise (Zdenka) Martin Winkler (Count Waldner) Anne Sofie von Otter (Adelaide) Josef Wagner (Mandryka) Matthew Newlin (Matteo) Dean Power (Count Elemer) Roger Smeets (Count Dominik) Tyler Zimmerman (Count Lamoral) Madrid, Teatro Real, 9 February 2023.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jérémie Cuvillier</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309162300 +0100" stop="20260309170000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">InterMezzo</title>
    <category lang="pl">program muzyczny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419708.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309170000 +0100" stop="20260309174400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">The life I love - The pianist Menahem Pressler</title>
    <desc lang="pl">The life I love - The pianist Menahem Pressler The music world has known Menahem Pressler for more than half a century and mainly for his work with the famous Beaux Arts Trio. He was the heart of this ensemble and when in 2008 the trio decided to separate, it was not the end for Menahem Pressler's career - in fact it was the start of a most remarkable and successful path as a soloist and in 2013, the 90-year-old grand seigneur of the piano gave his long overdue debut with the Berliner Philharmoniker. In 'The life I love - the pianist Menahem Pressler', from talks with Pressler over excerpts from one of his Master Classes, to interviews with artists like Daniel Harding, Quatuor Ébene, Leonidas Kavakos or Daniel Hope, we will gain deep insights into the life of this enchantingly 'venerable prodigy'. Menahem Pressler died on May 6, 2023 Directed by Grete Liffers 2014.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Grete Liffers</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419736.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309174400 +0100" stop="20260309203000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Grigory Sokolov at the Berlin Philharmonie : Schubert, Beethoven, Rameau</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Bruno Monsaingeon</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309203000 +0100" stop="20260309224000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Monteverdi from Mantua to Venice - John Eliot Gardiner</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sébastien Glas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2023</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984459.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309224000 +0100" stop="20260310002400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">John Eliot Gardiner - Monteverdi: Vespro della Beata Vergine - Versailles</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Stéphan Aubé</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2014</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310002400 +0100" stop="20260310015400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Prix de Lausanne: Rising Stars Gala 2026</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Lausanne, Théâtre de Beaulieu, 8 February 2026.</desc>
    <date>2026</date>
    <category lang="pl">balet</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419696.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310015400 +0100" stop="20260310034500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Claudio Abbado, Berliner Philharmoniker: Beethoven, Brahms, Dvorák</title>
    <date>2002</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310034500 +0100" stop="20260310062000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Richter, the Enigma</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Bruno Monsaingeon</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1997</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984494.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310062000 +0100" stop="20260310070800 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Mel Lewis Orchestra - Multiplatino</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Sandro Pedrazzetti</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1985</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310070800 +0100" stop="20260310075900 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">McCoy Tyner: Piano Solo</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Janos Darvas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>1983</date>
    <category lang="pl">jazz concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310075900 +0100" stop="20260310102300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Grigory Sokolov at the Berlin Philharmonie : Schubert, Beethoven, Rameau</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Bruno Monsaingeon</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2013</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310102300 +0100" stop="20260310114500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Jean-Yves Thibaudet, San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, Esa-Pekka Salonen: Scriabin - Prometheus</title>
    <desc lang="pl">San Francisco Symphony Orchestra, Esa-Pekka Salonen (conductor) Jean-Yves Thibaudet (piano) Mathilde Laurent (perfumer) Alexander Scriabin 1872 - 1915 Prometheus, The Poem of Fire Alexander Scriabin's symphonic poem 'Prometheus, The Poem of Fire' celebrates synesthesia and cosmic unity. Devised by San Francisco Symphony Music Director Esa-Pekka Salonen, pianist Jean-Yves Thibaudet, and Cartier in-house perfumer Mathilde Laurent, the San Francisco Symphony and Cartier present a multisensory production of 'Prometheus'. This collaborative world premiere combines dynamic musical and light performance with olfactory curation, subsuming audiences in Scriabin's creative vision more than a century after the piece of total art was composed. Directed by Sébastien Glas San Francisco, Davies Symphony Hall, 3 mars 2024.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Sébastien Glas</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310114500 +0100" stop="20260310164500 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Wagner : Götterdämmerung - Opernhaus Zurich</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Götterdämmerung Third day in three acts of 'Der Ring des Nibelungen' by Richard Wagner (1813 - 1883) Libretto by Richard Wagner Bayreuth, Festspielhaus, 17 aout 1876 Philharmonia Zürich Gianandrea Noseda (conductor) Andreas Homoki (Stage direction) Christian Schmidt (Set and Costume Design), Franck Evin (Lighting design) Klaus Florian Vogt (Siegfried) Daniel Schmutzhard (Gunther) Christopher Purves (Alberich) David Leigh (Hagen) Camilla Nylund (Brünnhilde) Lauren Fagan (Gutrune) Sarah Ferede (Waltraute) Freya Apffelstaedt (Erste Norn) Lena Sutor-Wernich (Zweite Norn) Giselle Allen (Dritte Norn) Uliana Alexyuk (Woglinde) Niamh O'Sullivan (Wellgunde) Siena Licht Miller (Floßhilde) Zurich, Opernhaus, 26 May 2024.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Michael Beyer</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984463.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310164500 +0100" stop="20260310181100 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Scott Ross - Traces of a Shooting Star 1951 - 1989</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Scott Ross - Traces of a Shooting Star 1951 - 1989 Scott on the Ross, about the recording of the 555 sonatas of Domenico Scarlatti Villeneuve lez Avignon, Tinel, April 1985 Produced by Bernard Tournois and Martina Catella Les maîtres de musique - Works by Domenico Scarlatti and Padre Antonio Soler Domenico Scarlatti 1685 - 1757 Sonata in D minor K 1 Sonata in A major K 6 Sonata in F sharp minor K 25 Sonata in B minor K 27 Sonata in E major K 380 Sonata in E major K 381 Sonata in A major K 208 Sonata in A major K 209 Antonio Soler 1729 - 1783 2 sonatas in D minor R 49 &amp; R 15 2 sonatas in F major R 56 &amp; R 69 Fandango R 146 Paris, Théâtre du Ranelagh, May 7, 1988 Directed by Georges Bessonnet Digital restoration 2024.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Bernard Tournois</director>
      <director>Martina Catella</director>
      <director>Georges Bessonnet</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2024</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984459.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310181100 +0100" stop="20260310182300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Steinway &amp; Sons</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Go behind the scenes at the Steinway &amp; Sons factory and discover Spirio, the incredible technology that allows a piano to replay a performance exactly as it was played live. Mr. Guido Zimmermann, the president of the world-famous pianomakers, talks us through the revolutionary concept, accompanied by images of the precise, fascinating craftmanship and engineering that goes into each one of the Spirio pianos. Hugo Cohen Sprung's documentary also allows us insight into French pianist and Steinway artist Bertrand Chamayou's experience with the technology and features a preview of his unique two-piano concert in which he performs with his 'shadow'.</desc>
    <date>2025</date>
    <category lang="pl">film dokumentalny</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984494.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310182300 +0100" stop="20260310203000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Orchestre de Paris, Khatia Buniatishvili, Klaus Mäkelä: Falla, Tchaikovsky, Debussy, Ravel</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Isabelle Soulard</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310203000 +0100" stop="20260310215400 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">La Grande Danza - Aterballetto in Milan</title>
    <desc lang="pl">La grande danza - Aterballetto in Milan Choreographies by Jirí Pokorny (Words &amp; Space), Giuseppe Spota (Narcissus), Philippe Kratz (Phoenix) Aterballetto is the principal producing and touring dance company in Italy. They are well-known for their ability to shift their style across a wide range of musical genres, from classical to pop and jazz. Jirí Pokorny's 'Words and Space' is a metaphor of an intrapersonal speech, a book full of floating stories. It is personal, intimate, and very poetic. 'Phoenix' is inspired by the idea of the infinite circular motion of life: Birth, growth, immobility, death and finally birth once again. Choreographer Philippe Kratz tries to understand who we were and what we are capable to become. In 'Narcissus' Giuseppe Spota takes a look at the youth of today. Are they ready to come out of their virtual frames and face the mirror ofeveryday life? Or will they all end up like Narcissus,alone to admire and cherish themselves? Directed by Andreas Morell.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Andreas Morell</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2017</date>
    <category lang="pl">balet</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4419696.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310215400 +0100" stop="20260310232000 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Rafael Payare, Orchestre symphonique de Montréal: Ravel, Shostakovich</title>
    <credits>
      <director>Claudine Gamache</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2021</date>
    <category lang="pl">classical concert</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa4984469.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260310232000 +0100" stop="20260311021300 +0100" channel="MEZZO">
    <title lang="pl">Puccini: Il Trittico - Théâtre de la Monnaie</title>
    <desc lang="pl">Il Trittico Three operas in one act by Giacomo Puccini 1858 -1924 Il Tabarro Libretto by Giuseppe Adami, based on 'La Houppelande' by Didier Gold Suor Angelica Libretto by Giovacchino Forzano Gianni Schicchi Libretto by Giovacchino Forzano, based on an episode in Dante's 'Divine Comedy' First performance in New York, Metropolitan Opera, December 14, 1918 La Monnaie Symphony Orchestra and Choirs, La Monnaie Children's and Youth Choirs, Alain Altinoglu (Musical Direction) Alberto Moro (Choir leader) Tobias Kratzer (Director) Rainer Sellmaier (Sets &amp; costumes), Bernd Purkrabek (Lighting), Manuel Braun (Video) Il Tabarro Peter Kálmán (Michele) Corinne Winters (Giorgetta) Adam Smith (Luigi Amante) Roberto Covatta (Il Tinca) Giovanni Furlanetto (Il Talpa) Maxime Melnik (Un venditore di canzonette) Annunziata Vestri (La Frugola) Benedetta Torre (Amante) Suor Angelica Corinne Winters (Suor Angelica) Raehann Bryce-Davis (La zia principessa) Elena Zilio (La badessa) Annunziata Vestri (La suora zelatrice) Tineke Van Ingelgem (La maestra delle novizie La suora infirmiera) Benedetta Torre (Suor Genovieffa) Annelies Kerstens (Suor Osmina) Raphaële Green (Suor Dolcina) Karen Vermeiren (Prima sorella cercatrice) Marta Beretta (Seconda sorella cercatrice) Emma Posman (Una novizia) Gianni Schicchi Peter Kálmán (Gianni Schicchi) Benedetta Torre (Lauretta) Elena Zilio (Zita) Adam Smith (Rinuccio) Roberto Covatta (Gherardo) Karen Vermeiren (Nella) Luca Dall'Amico (Betto di Signa) Giovanni Furlanetto (Simone) Gabriele Nani (Marco) Tineke Van Ingelgem (La Ciesca) Roberto Accurso (Maestro Spinelloccio Ser Amantio di Nicolao) Kurt Gysen (Pinellino) Lucas Cortoos (Guccio) Henri de Beauffort (Gherardino) Gerard Lavalle (Buoso Donati) Brussels, Théâtre de la Monnaie / De Munt, April 30, 2022.</desc>
    <credits>
      <director>Jérémie Cuvillier</director>
    </credits>
    <date>2022</date>
    <category lang="pl">opera</category>
    <icon src="https://ptv-prod.wpcdn.pl/media/akpa5028629.jpg" />
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305004500 +0100" stop="20260305023000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Kielce - Sporting</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305023000 +0100" stop="20260305024500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Zlaté okamžiky</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305024500 +0100" stop="20260305053000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">HK Nitra - HK Poprad</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Tipsport Liga, 51. koloTipsport Liga, 51. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305053000 +0100" stop="20260305060000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305060000 +0100" stop="20260305073000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305073000 +0100" stop="20260305100000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Färjestad - Växjö</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní částSHL, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305100000 +0100" stop="20260305110000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305110000 +0100" stop="20260305114500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Richard Varga</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305114500 +0100" stop="20260305123000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Andrej Sekera</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305123000 +0100" stop="20260305154500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Badou Jack - Noel Mikaelian</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Los AngelesLos Angeles.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305154500 +0100" stop="20260305161500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305161500 +0100" stop="20260305171500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Serie A, 27. kolo</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305171500 +0100" stop="20260305174500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Secrets of Calcio (Tajemství fotbalu), Carlo Ancelotti</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305174500 +0100" stop="20260305194500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Slovensko - Rumunsko</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305194500 +0100" stop="20260305204500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Miguel Angel Cotto - Carlos Ramirez</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">novénové.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305204500 +0100" stop="20260305210000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Berat Djimsiti</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305210000 +0100" stop="20260305230000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Lazio - Atalanta</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifináleCoppa Italia, semifinále.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305230000 +0100" stop="20260305234500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Lukas Haraslin</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305234500 +0100" stop="20260306003000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Branko Radivojevič</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306003000 +0100" stop="20260306020000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Szeged - GOG</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306020000 +0100" stop="20260306033000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Nantes - Veszprém</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306033000 +0100" stop="20260306060000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Färjestad - Växjö</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní částSHL, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306060000 +0100" stop="20260306073000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306073000 +0100" stop="20260306100000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Frölunda - Lulea</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">CHL, fináleCHL, finále.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306100000 +0100" stop="20260306110000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306110000 +0100" stop="20260306120000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Serie A, 27. kolo</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306120000 +0100" stop="20260306140000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifinále</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306140000 +0100" stop="20260306160000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifinále</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306160000 +0100" stop="20260306163000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306163000 +0100" stop="20260306171500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Ján Lašák</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306171500 +0100" stop="20260306174500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">nové</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306174500 +0100" stop="20260306204500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">HC Košice - Vlci Žilina</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Tipsport Liga, 53. koloTipsport Liga, 53. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306204500 +0100" stop="20260306224500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Serie A, 28. kolo</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306224500 +0100" stop="20260307020000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Callum Simpson - Troy Williamson</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">LeedsLeeds.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307020000 +0100" stop="20260307040000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Como - Inter</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifináleCoppa Italia, semifinále.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307040000 +0100" stop="20260307060000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifinále</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307060000 +0100" stop="20260307073000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307073000 +0100" stop="20260307093000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifinále</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307093000 +0100" stop="20260307100000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307100000 +0100" stop="20260307110000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307110000 +0100" stop="20260307150000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Šipky</title>
    <desc lang="cs">Poland Darts Open, PDC European Tour 2025, 3. den, část 2Poland Darts Open, PDC European Tour 2025, 3. den, část 2.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307150000 +0100" stop="20260307170000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Cagliari - Como</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307170000 +0100" stop="20260307180000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Miguel Angel Cotto - Carlos Ramirez</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307180000 +0100" stop="20260307200000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Atalanta - Udienese</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307200000 +0100" stop="20260307204500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Lukas Haraslin</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307204500 +0100" stop="20260307224500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Juventus - Pisa</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307224500 +0100" stop="20260308004500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Atalanta - Udienese</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308004500 +0100" stop="20260308031500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">ZSC Lions - Davos</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Národní liga, základní částNárodní liga, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308031500 +0100" stop="20260308060000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Callum Simpson - Troy Williamson</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">LeedsLeeds.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308060000 +0100" stop="20260308073000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308073000 +0100" stop="20260308100000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Malmö - Skelleftea</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní částSHL, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308100000 +0100" stop="20260308110000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308110000 +0100" stop="20260308120000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Miguel Angel Cotto - Carlos Ramirez</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308120000 +0100" stop="20260308121500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Yerry Mina</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308121500 +0100" stop="20260308123000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Riccardo Orsoloni</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308123000 +0100" stop="20260308143000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Lecce - Cremonese</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308143000 +0100" stop="20260308150000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Sectrets of Calcio (Tajemství fotbalu), La Gazetta</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308150000 +0100" stop="20260308170000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Bologna - Verona</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308170000 +0100" stop="20260308180000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Antonio Tarver vs Eric Harding</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308180000 +0100" stop="20260308200000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Janov - Řím</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308200000 +0100" stop="20260308204500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Ján Lašák</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308204500 +0100" stop="20260308224500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Milán - Inter</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308224500 +0100" stop="20260309011500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">ZSC Lions - Davos</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Národní liga, základní částNárodní liga, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309011500 +0100" stop="20260309034500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Malmö - Skelleftea</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní částSHL, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309034500 +0100" stop="20260309053000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rumunsko - Slovensko</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309053000 +0100" stop="20260309060000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Tenis, WTA 250, Cluj Napoca, sestřih</title>
    <desc lang="cs">Tenisová WTA Tour je nejvyšší úroveň ženského profesionálního tenisu, která zahrnuje desítky turnajů v sezoně.Tenisová WTA Tour je nejvyšší úroveň ženského profesionálního tenisu, která zahrnuje desítky turnajů v sezoně.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309060000 +0100" stop="20260309073000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309073000 +0100" stop="20260309100000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">ZSC Lions - Davos</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Národní liga, základní částNárodní liga, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309100000 +0100" stop="20260309110000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309110000 +0100" stop="20260309141500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Callum Simpson - Troy Williamson</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">LeedsLeeds.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309141500 +0100" stop="20260309160000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Aalborg - Füchse Berlín</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309160000 +0100" stop="20260309174500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Kielce - Sporting</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309174500 +0100" stop="20260309183000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Branko Radivojevič</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309183000 +0100" stop="20260309203000 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Neapol - Turín</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309203000 +0100" stop="20260309204500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Jacopo Fazzini</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309204500 +0100" stop="20260309224500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Lazio - Sassuolo</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309224500 +0100" stop="20260309234500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">EL/EKL, upoutávka, nové</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309234500 +0100" stop="20260310004500 +0100" channel="Sport 1">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Miguel Angel Cotto - Carlos Ramirez</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305011500 +0100" stop="20260305031500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Lazio - Atalanta</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifináleCoppa Italia, semifinále.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305031500 +0100" stop="20260305051500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Verona - Neapol</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305051500 +0100" stop="20260305060000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Branko Radivojevič</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305060000 +0100" stop="20260305080000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Como - Lecce</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305080000 +0100" stop="20260305090000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305090000 +0100" stop="20260305110000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Inter - Janov</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305110000 +0100" stop="20260305120000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305120000 +0100" stop="20260305140000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Tenis</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">WTA 250, Austin, finále</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Tenisová WTA Tour je nejvyšší úroveň ženského profesionálního tenisu, která zahrnuje desítky turnajů v sezoně.Tenisová WTA Tour je nejvyšší úroveň ženského profesionálního tenisu, která zahrnuje desítky turnajů v sezoně.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305140000 +0100" stop="20260305150000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Poker</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">WSOP, sestřih hlavních událostí 15/15</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305150000 +0100" stop="20260305153000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305153000 +0100" stop="20260305163000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Miguel Angel Cotto - Carlos Ramirez</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305163000 +0100" stop="20260305183000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Řím - Juventus</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305183000 +0100" stop="20260305184500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Hakan Çalhanoğlu</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305184500 +0100" stop="20260305203000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Szeged - GOG</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305203000 +0100" stop="20260305204500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Johan Vásquez</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305204500 +0100" stop="20260305223000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Nantes - Veszprém</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260305223000 +0100" stop="20260306003000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Malmö - Färjestad</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní část, dnešníSHL, základní část, dnešní.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306003000 +0100" stop="20260306023000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Slovensko - Rumunsko</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306023000 +0100" stop="20260306043000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Lazio - Atalanta</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifináleCoppa Italia, semifinále.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306043000 +0100" stop="20260306053000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Poker</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">WSOP, sestřih hlavních událostí 15/15</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306053000 +0100" stop="20260306060000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306060000 +0100" stop="20260306080000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Řím - Juventus</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306080000 +0100" stop="20260306090000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306090000 +0100" stop="20260306110000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Turín - Lazio</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306110000 +0100" stop="20260306120000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306120000 +0100" stop="20260306121500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Samuele Ricci</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306121500 +0100" stop="20260306161500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Šipky</title>
    <desc lang="cs">Poland Darts Open, PDC European Tour 2025, 3. den, část 1Poland Darts Open, PDC European Tour 2025, 3. den, část 1.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306161500 +0100" stop="20260306183000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Evropská liga, Ligová fáze</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306183000 +0100" stop="20260306204500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Evropská liga, Ligová fáze</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306204500 +0100" stop="20260306214500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Miguel Angel Cotto - Carlos Ramirez</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306214500 +0100" stop="20260306221500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">nové</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260306221500 +0100" stop="20260307011500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Tipsport Liga, 53. kolo</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307011500 +0100" stop="20260307031500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Neapol - Turín</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307031500 +0100" stop="20260307051500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Slovensko - Rumunsko</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307051500 +0100" stop="20260307060000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">MVP</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Rozhovory o sportu, Branko Radivojevič</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307060000 +0100" stop="20260307080000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Turín - Lazio</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307080000 +0100" stop="20260307090000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307090000 +0100" stop="20260307110000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Verona - Neapol</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 27. koloSerie A, 27. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307110000 +0100" stop="20260307120000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307120000 +0100" stop="20260307150000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">HC Košice - Vlci Žilina</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Tipsport Liga, 53. koloTipsport Liga, 53. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307150000 +0100" stop="20260307151500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Robin Gosens</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307151500 +0100" stop="20260307174500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Malmö - Skelleftea</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní částSHL, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307174500 +0100" stop="20260307180000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Made in Italy, Hakan Çalhanoğlu</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307180000 +0100" stop="20260307194500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Aalborg - Füchse Berlín</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307194500 +0100" stop="20260307221500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">ZSC Lions - Davos</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Národní liga, základní částNárodní liga, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260307221500 +0100" stop="20260308001500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Växjö - Örebro</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní část, dnešníSHL, základní část, dnešní.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308001500 +0100" stop="20260308021500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Atalanta - Udienese</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308021500 +0100" stop="20260308041500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Juventus - Pisa</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308041500 +0100" stop="20260308060000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Nantes - Veszprém</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308060000 +0100" stop="20260308080000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Cagliari - Como</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308080000 +0100" stop="20260308090000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308090000 +0100" stop="20260308110000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Atalanta - Udinese</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308110000 +0100" stop="20260308120000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308120000 +0100" stop="20260308143000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">ZSC Lions - Davos</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Národní liga, základní částNárodní liga, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308143000 +0100" stop="20260308170000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Malmö - Skelleftea</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">SHL, základní částSHL, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308170000 +0100" stop="20260308180000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Poker</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">WSOP, sestřih hlavních událostí 15/15</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308180000 +0100" stop="20260308194500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Aalborg - Füchse Berlín</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308194500 +0100" stop="20260308230000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Box</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Callum Simpson - Troy Williamson</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">LeedsLeeds.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260308230000 +0100" stop="20260309010000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Bologna - Verona</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309010000 +0100" stop="20260309030000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Janov - Řím</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309030000 +0100" stop="20260309050000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Milán - Inter</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309050000 +0100" stop="20260309060000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Poker</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">WSOP, sestřih hlavních událostí 15/15</sub-title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309060000 +0100" stop="20260309080000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Bologna - Verona</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309080000 +0100" stop="20260309090000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309090000 +0100" stop="20260309110000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Lecce - Cremonese</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Serie A, 28. koloSerie A, 28. kolo.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309110000 +0100" stop="20260309120000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Televizní nákupy</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309120000 +0100" stop="20260309133000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Szeged - GOG</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Liga mistrů, muži, základní skupinaLiga mistrů, muži, základní skupina.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309133000 +0100" stop="20260309153000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Como - Inter</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifináleCoppa Italia, semifinále.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309153000 +0100" stop="20260309173000 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Lazio - Atalanta</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Coppa Italia, semifináleCoppa Italia, semifinále.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309173000 +0100" stop="20260309191500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Házená</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Slovensko - Rumunsko</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026EHF, Evropský pohár, ženy, 2026.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309191500 +0100" stop="20260309194500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Fotbal</title>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309194500 +0100" stop="20260309221500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">Davos - Biel</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Národní liga, základní částNárodní liga, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  <programme start="20260309221500 +0100" stop="20260310004500 +0100" channel="Sport 2">
    <title lang="cs">Lední hokej</title>
    <sub-title lang="cs">ZSC Lions - Davos</sub-title>
    <desc lang="cs">Národní liga, základní částNárodní liga, základní část.</desc>
    <category lang="cs">Sport</category>
  </programme>
  </tv>